;[
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'A client wants to improve their deadlift. Which of the following is an outcome goal?',
    answer: 'I want to deadlift 300 pounds.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'I want to deadlift 300 pounds.|I want to lift 3 times per week.|I want to deadlift after work.|I want to deadlift once per week.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question: 'Which of the following is an open-ended question?',
    answer: 'What has prevented you from reaching your goals in the past?',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'What has prevented you from reaching your goals in the past?|What do you currently weigh?|Did you exercise this week?|Have you experienced barriers to reaching your goals?',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which leadership component refers to the leader being a great example for how to live a healthy and balanced life, which includes being optimistic, empathetic, and knowledgeable?',
    answer: "Leader's qualities",
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "Leader's qualities|Leader's style|The requirements of the leader|The personality of the leader",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'What stage of change is a person in if they have been exercising but for less than 6 months?',
    answer: 'Action',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Action|Contemplation|Maintenance|Precontemplation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Changing leadership style based on the size of a group would be an example of which component of leadership?',
    answer: 'Situational factors',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "Situational factors|Follower's qualities|Leader's qualities|Leadership styles",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'The field of psychology focuses on which of the following domains?',
    answer: 'The mind and behavior',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The mind and behavior\n' +
      '|Physiological systems\n' +
      '|Pathology of disease\n' +
      '|Neuromuscular adaptations\n' +
      '',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question: 'What type of imagery involves focusing on exercise form?',
    answer: 'Technique imagery',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Technique imagery|Appearance imagery|Energy imagery|Cognitive fusion',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'When it comes to exercise, older adults find which of the following to be the most motivating?',
    answer: 'Health and well-being',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Health and well-being|Competition with others|Improved physical appearance|Being a part of a social group',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'What type of imagery occurs when a client imagines health-related outcomes?',
    answer: 'Appearance imagery',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Appearance imagery|Energy imagery|Technique imagery|Positive self-talk',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'When it comes to barriers to exercise, which statement is correct?',
    answer:
      'Barriers to exercise are often cited by people who are sedentary or infrequently active.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Barriers to exercise are often cited by people who are sedentary or infrequently active.|All individuals have "lack of time" as a barrier.|Barriers never change; therefore, individuals need to focus on motives.|It is impossible to ever fully overcome all barriers.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'If a client is using social media to find inspiration, information, or support for their fitness endeavors, it would be an example of which social construct?',
    answer: 'Social influence',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Social influence|Social pressure|Social connections|Social ambivalence',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which barrier to exercise is most likely to be associated with body image issues?',
    answer: 'Social physique anxiety',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Social physique anxiety|Lack of social support|Unrealistic goals|Ambivalence',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'A Certified Personal Trainer asks a client who is not currently doing any aerobic training how ready they are to do aerobic training one time per week for 30 minutes using a scale of 1 through 10, with 1 representing not at all ready and 10 representing completely ready. They say they are at a 1; what stage of change are they in?',
    answer: 'Precontemplation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Precontemplation|Action|Preparation|Maintenance',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'A Certified Personal Trainer is speaking with a client who is not currently doing any consistent aerobic training. They ask how ready the client is to do aerobic training once a week for 30 minutes, using a scale of 1 to 10, with 1 representing "not at all ready" and 10 representing "completely ready." If the client is at a 9, what stage of change are they in?',
    answer: 'Preparation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Preparation|Action|Precontemplation|Maintenance',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question: 'Which of the following would be considered a process goal?',
    answer: 'Run three times a week',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Run three times a week\n' +
      '|Run one mile\n' +
      '|Squat 100 pounds\n' +
      '|Run a 10k race\n' +
      '',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'The social standing of a person or group that includes education, income, and occupation describes which term?',
    answer: 'Socioeconomic status',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Socioeconomic status|Net worth|Social influence|Income status',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'If a new client indicates that they are frustrated with their lack of expected results, which barrier are they likely experiencing?',
    answer: 'Unrealistic goals',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Unrealistic goals|Social physique anxiety|Lack of social support|Ambivalence',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'A client wants to improve their mile time. Which of the following is an outcome goal?',
    answer: 'I want to run a 6-minute mile.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'I want to run a 6-minute mile.|I want to run 3 times per week.|I want to run in the morning before work.|I want to run outside.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'A new client is having trouble managing her busy schedule and has cancelled her last 3 personal training sessions. What is the best option for the fitness professional?',
    answer:
      'Help the client determine her barriers, and talk through strategies to overcome them.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Help the client determine her barriers, and talk through strategies to overcome them.|Let the client know that cancelling sessions costs them money without providing any benefits.|Politely let the client know that you are transferring them to another trainer.|Refund the remaining sessions and actively search for a new client.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'A community could influence physical activity for its inhabitants by doing which of the following?',
    answer: 'Creating more green spaces, playgrounds, and walking trails',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Creating more green spaces, playgrounds, and walking trails|Allowing more permits for fitness facilities to open|Reducing the number of fast-food restaurants|Limiting the number of sports leagues that are using a community center',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'A client who has been training consistently for over a year has indicated that he wants to find more efficient ways to exercise at home. Which type of social support does he need?',
    answer: 'Informational support',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Informational support|Companionship support|Instrumental support|Emotional support',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Adjusting daily priorities is a strategy to overcome which of the following barriers?',
    answer: 'Lack of time',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Lack of time|Unrealistic goals|Convenience|Ambivalence',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question: 'Social physique anxiety is best defined by which statement?',
    answer:
      'When someone feels insecure about how they think others are viewing their body',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'When someone feels insecure about how they think others are viewing their body|When someone has anxiety about social situations|When someone has general anxiety about physical activity|When someone has anxiety about how their physique looks in the mirror',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Ambivalent people may be reluctant to start an exercise program. What should the fitness professional focus on when helping a potential client overcome this barrier?',
    answer:
      'Probe further to determine other barriers they are experiencing and possible motives to participate.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Probe further to determine other barriers they are experiencing and possible motives to participate.|Provide information about the benefits of participating and hope they decide to participate.|Let them know you understand it is a difficult decision to participate and you will give them time to think about it.|Let them know that you will not take no for an answer because exercise is good for everyone.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'What might a Certified Personal Trainer do for someone in the precontemplation stage of change?',
    answer: 'Provide them with education and knowledge',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Provide them with education and knowledge|Encourage them to make plans to exercise|Tell them to exercise with a friend|Help them identify barriers to exercise',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Loaning some exercise bands to a client who is scheduled to go on vacation is an example of which type of social support?',
    answer: 'Instrumental support',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Instrumental support|Informational support|Companionship support|Emotional support',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Self-esteem and body image are said to have which type of relationship?',
    answer: 'Reciprocal',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Reciprocal|Autonomous|Unequal|Independent',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'A long-term client has recently indicated that she wants to start training for a fitness competition and, due to her competitive nature, she indicates that she wants to win. Which type of motivation is driving her?',
    answer: 'Extrinsic motivation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Extrinsic motivation|Intrinsic motivation|Affiliation motivation|Autonomy motivation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question: 'Social support is best described by which statement?',
    answer:
      'The intentional things that people do to assist others to achieve a specific behavior',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "The intentional things that people do to assist others to achieve a specific behavior|Providing counseling sessions with clients who exhibit signs of depression|Rearranging a schedule to accommodate a client's availability|Posting on social media about the recent successes of clients",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'The number of sidewalks available in a community is an example of which of the following?',
    answer: 'The built environment',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The built environment|The constructed environment|The manufactured environment|The assembled environment',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'What term is defined as the generic modifiable factors that impact behavior?',
    answer: 'Determinants',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Determinants|Behavior change techniques|Self-efficacy|Attitudes',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Individuals in this stage of change may sporadically engage in physical activity but without any form, structure, or consistency.',
    answer: 'Preparation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Preparation|Maintenance|Contemplation|Precontemplation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which term best describes when someone has mixed feelings about exercise and can see both the pros and cons of participating?',
    answer: 'Ambivalence',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Ambivalence|Confusion|Unequivocal|Ambiguity',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'What stage of change is a person in if they are planning to begin exercising soon and have taken steps toward it?',
    answer: 'Preparation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Preparation|Action|Maintenance|Precontemplation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'What type of communication includes posture, hand gestures, proximity to others, and facial expressions?',
    answer: 'Nonverbal communication',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Nonverbal communication|Verbal communication|Reflective listening|Motivational interviewing',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question: 'Which of the following is true about body image?',
    answer:
      'Body image may not match reality, and people may view their bodies in a negative way and evaluate themselves inaccurately.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Body image may not match reality, and people may view their bodies in a negative way and evaluate themselves inaccurately.|Body image is measured accurately based on an individual evaluating a picture of themselves.|Body image is more positive in individuals who regularly exercise in a group setting.|Body image is a very stable variable and, once established, rarely changes for an individual.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'When a client makes a plan, such as, "When I am done with work, I will run for 30 minutes," what are they doing?',
    answer: 'Forming an implementation intention',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Forming an implementation intention|Self-monitoring|Creating a coping plan|Stating an outcome expectation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      "Which communication technique allows the fitness professional to show appreciation of a client's strengths?",
    answer: 'Affirmations',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Affirmations|Reflections|Collecting summaries|Transitional summaries',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which source of social support has been shown to be particularly important for older adults?',
    answer: 'Family',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Family|Exercise leader|Exercise group|The community',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Not having someone to exercise with would be an example of which type of barrier?',
    answer: 'Lack of social support',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Lack of social support|Lack of willpower|Lack of motivation|Lack of convenience',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'When a client makes a statement that supports their current behavior, what is this called?',
    answer: 'Sustain talk',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Sustain talk|Change talk|An affirmation|A collecting summary',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which type of professionals are qualified to counsel individuals who are diagnosed with depression, using exercise as a supplemental treatment?',
    answer: 'Psychologist or psychiatrist',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Psychologist or psychiatrist|Registered dietitian or nutritionist|Corrective exercise specialist or certified exercise physiologist|Certified Personal Trainer or certified fitness professional',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which source of social support for exercise is the most influential for children and adolescents?',
    answer: 'Parents',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Parents|Peers|Exercise groups|The community',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question: 'What is the correct order of the Stages of Change?',
    answer: 'Precontemplation, contemplation, preparation, action, maintenance',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Precontemplation, contemplation, preparation, action, maintenance|Contemplation, precontemplation, preparation, action, maintenance|Precontemplation, action, preparation, contemplation, maintenance|Preparation, precontemplation, contemplation, action, maintenance',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question: 'Which scenario best demonstrates companionship support?',
    answer:
      'Coordinating group events that are centered around physical activities',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Coordinating group events that are centered around physical activities|Taking someone shopping to purchase attire for exercise|Making time to talk to clients about how their exercise program is going|Creating handouts for clients that cover topics about fitness and wellness',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'When a person is thinking about implementing change but has not yet taken any steps to get started, what stage of change are they likely in?',
    answer: 'Contemplation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Contemplation\n|Action\n|Precontemplation\n|Maintenance\n',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Providing encouragement and being empathetic is an example of which type of social support?',
    answer: 'Emotional support',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Emotional support|Informational support|Companionship support|Instrumental support',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      "A Certified Personal Trainer has been listening to a client's goals. After the client is done speaking, the trainer restates the goals back to the client. What best describes the approach the trainer is using?",
    answer: 'Reflective listening',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Reflective listening|Active listening|Nonverbal communication|Motivational interviewing',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'When a client indicates that she finds it difficult to complete a workout on her own, she is likely in need of which type of support?',
    answer: 'Companionship support',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Companionship support|Instrumental support|Informational support|Emotional support',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      "Without a perceived discrepancy between a client's current state and making a change, what is lacking?",
    answer: 'Motivation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Motivation|Self-efficacy|Autonomy|Positive outcome expectation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question: 'Which statement best demonstrates empathy?',
    answer:
      'I know that finding time to exercise is hard. I struggle to get it done sometimes as well.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "I know that finding time to exercise is hard. I struggle to get it done sometimes as well.|If you spend more time in the gym, you will reach your goals faster.|I think you will feel healthier once you finally lose some weight.|I don't understand why you think it's so hard to do 30 minutes of cardio 3 times a week.",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'What type of listening involves making a best guess as to what the speaker means, then stating it back to the speaker?',
    answer: 'Reflective listening',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Reflective listening|Active listening|Affirming|Motivational interviewing',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'If a Certified Personal Trainer helps a client make an action plan to enhance their confidence that they can exercise on their own, what determinant of behavior are they targeting?',
    answer: 'Self-efficacy',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Self-efficacy|Intention|Attitudes|Outcome expectations',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question: 'Informational support would be provided by which example?',
    answer:
      'Teaching a client how many minutes of cardio they should be accumulating each day',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Teaching a client how many minutes of cardio they should be accumulating each day|Letting a client know they are not alone in the process of losing weight|Working out alongside a client|Holding the client accountable to lifting weights 3 days per week',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which type of motivation would be characterized by a client who enjoys the process of becoming more fit?',
    answer: 'Intrinsic motivation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Intrinsic motivation|Extrinsic motivation|Achievement motivation|Affiliation motivation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Research has demonstrated that moderate-intensity exercise is best for which of the following?',
    answer: 'Providing psychological benefits',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Providing psychological benefits|Winning a triathlon|Developing intrinsic motivation|Reducing burnout',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'If a Certified Personal Trainer helps a client improve their technique by using guided practice to enhance confidence, what determinant of behavior are they targeting?',
    answer: 'Self-efficacy',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Self-efficacy|Intention|Self-regulation|Outcome expectations',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'At the beginning of an exercise session, a client has shared that they are in a bad mood and would rather skip the session. Which of the following observations should the fitness professional share with the client?',
    answer:
      'Exercise is known to improve mood, even with bouts as short as 10 minutes, so exercise is a good remedy.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Exercise is known to improve mood, even with bouts as short as 10 minutes, so exercise is a good remedy.|Exercise is known to exacerbate a bad mood; therefore, stopping the session is a good idea.|Exercise can only affect mood when done for at least 60 minutes, so it would be best to stay longer than normal.|Exercise cannot improve mood, so it would be best to reschedule the session for another day.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'A benefit of being part of an exercise group includes comradery, which is described by which of the following statements?',
    answer:
      'Participants are forming connections with people who are attempting to achieve similar results, while experiencing feelings of friendship, closeness, and loyalty.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Participants are forming connections with people who are attempting to achieve similar results, while experiencing feelings of friendship, closeness, and loyalty.|When a group or situation is warm and inviting, it brings people together; when people feel welcome, they are likely to return.|Participants are encouraged to push as hard as they can and may work harder in the presence of the group.|Participants have people they can compare themselves with. Being able to see what others can do and achieve can serve as further motivation.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question: 'Self-esteem is defined by which of the following?',
    answer:
      'How someone evaluates their own self-worth physically, emotionally, and socially',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'How someone evaluates their own self-worth physically, emotionally, and socially|How someone views their physical self or how they visualize their body|When someone is anxious about how others view their body|How someone conceptualizes their place in society',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question: 'Social physique anxiety is more prevalent in which population?',
    answer: 'Females',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Females|Males|People with a low body mass index|People with a low body fat percentage',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'A client is asked, "Why do you want to lose weight?" This is an example of what kind of question?',
    answer: 'Open-ended',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Open-ended|Directive|Closed-ended|Contemplation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which of the following reasons for group exercise participation is described as having a schedule and being able to anticipate what the exercise experience will be like?',
    answer: 'Consistency',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Consistency|Mindlessness|Intensity|Accountability',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'What is a client-centric coaching style that helps enhance their desire to change by resolving ambivalence?',
    answer: 'Motivational interviewing',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Motivational interviewing|Collecting summaries|Affirming|Reflective listening',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Having an informal role in an exercise group is demonstrated by which example?',
    answer: 'Planning social gatherings for the group',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Planning social gatherings for the group|Planning the workout for the group|Setting the time for the group to meet|Providing modifications during the workout',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Having poor body image is most likely to be associated with which of the following?',
    answer: 'Low self-esteem',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Low self-esteem|Low body mass index|Low levels of motivation|Low levels of social support',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which of the following is a behavior change technique where clients list potential barriers and make plans to overcome them?',
    answer: 'Coping responses',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Coping responses|Implementation intentions|Self-monitoring|Resisting social pressure',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'A client who has been training for 6 months has recently moved farther from the fitness facility. Which barrier should she be preparing to overcome?',
    answer: 'Convenience',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Convenience|Lack of social support|Lack of time|Ambivalence',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which of the following is a question that may provoke resistance?',
    answer: 'What makes you think you are not at risk?',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'What makes you think you are not at risk?|What might you want to change?|If you decided to make a change, what might you do?|What might work for you?',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'A client has been journaling their behavior. They find that if they get home and sit on the couch to watch television, they do not end up exercising. But if they bring their gym clothes to work with them and change before leaving the office, they are more likely to exercise. Which behavior change technique are they using?',
    answer: 'Self-monitoring',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Self-monitoring|Action planning|Coping planning|Goal setting',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      "Which of the following is an example of a client's intrinsic motivation for exercise?",
    answer: 'Exercising because it is fun',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Exercising because it is fun|Exercising because a doctor tells them to|Exercising because they feel guilty|Exercising because they value the health benefits',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which type of support describes the actions that a person takes to help another person engage in exercise?',
    answer: 'Instrumental support',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Instrumental support|Companionship support|Emotional support|Informational support',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question: 'Which of the following most closely resembles a SMART goal?',
    answer: 'I want to lose 20 pounds over the next 8 months.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'I want to lose 20 pounds over the next 8 months.|I want to lose 20 pounds in the next month.|I want to lose weight.|I want to lose 20 pounds.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which behavior change technique allows individuals to identify external triggers that lead them to behave in certain ways?',
    answer: 'Self-monitoring',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Self-monitoring|Action planning|Enlisting social support|Coping planning',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      "A Certified Personal Trainer wants to improve a client's outcome expectations for resistance training. What behavior change technique might they use?",
    answer: 'Providing information on the health benefits',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Providing information on the health benefits|Improving their confidence for their technique|Helping them make a plan|Helping make the exercises fun',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      "The impact that family members, peers, or coworkers have over someone's decision to exercise describes which of the following terms?",
    answer: 'Group influence',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Group influence|Societal influence|Peer pressure|Health influence',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'An important aspect of an established exercise group includes which of the following?',
    answer: 'The group feels distinct from other people.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The group feels distinct from other people.|Once the group is formed, no other participants are allowed in.|Groups function only when all members are present.|Groups rely only on the leader for support.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Long-term exercise adherence is associated with which type of motivation?',
    answer: 'Intrinsic motivation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Intrinsic motivation|Extrinsic motivation|Amotivation|Incentive motivation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      "When a Certified Personal Trainer wants to enhance a client's self-efficacy by breaking down exercises or goals into easier-to-achieve tasks, what behavior change technique are they using?",
    answer: 'Set specific tasks',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Set specific tasks|Provide instructions|Experience mastery|Verbal persuasion',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Extrinsic motivation is characterized by which of the following?',
    answer:
      'Participating in an activity or behavior for some type of reward or recognition from others',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Participating in an activity or behavior for some type of reward or recognition from others|Being motivated by the process of changing behaviors|A drive to be good at something|Being motivated by a fear of failure',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'In a group exercise setting within a fitness facility, which person should greet all members, make everyone feel welcome, and ensure that participants have the right equipment and attire to participate safely?',
    answer: 'Exercise leader',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Exercise leader|Fitness manager|General manager|Certified Personal Trainer',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'What stage of change is a person in if they are not planning on exercising within the next 6 months?',
    answer: 'Precontemplation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Precontemplation|Action|Contemplation|Maintenance',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'What behavior change technique is a specific plan that drives behavior by identifying cues toward action?',
    answer: 'Implementation intention',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Implementation intention|Coping plan|Self-monitoring|Guided practice',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'A new client has indicated that they are exercising due to advice from their physician, but they are generally amotivated. What would be the best choice for the personal trainer in their initial meeting?',
    answer: 'Inquire further about what their motives are for participating.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Inquire further about what their motives are for participating.|Establish short- and long-term goals.|Create a plan for overcoming barriers.|Start establishing an emotional support system.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'What is the practice of identifying a negative inner narrative and replacing it with positive statements?',
    answer: 'Reverse listing',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Reverse listing|Stopping|Cognitive fusion|Imagery',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Intentions are a good predictor of behavior, but what has been shown to help translate intentions into behavior?',
    answer: 'Planning',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Planning|Outcome expectations|Action self-efficacy|Subjective norms',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'The intensity and direction of someone’s effort describes which of the following?',
    answer: 'Motivation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Motivation|Ambition|Initiative|Aspiration',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'What stage of change is a person in if they have been exercising consistently for 6 months or longer?',
    answer: 'Maintenance',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Maintenance|Action|Contemplation|Precontemplation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which barrier is most often cited as a top barrier among most individuals?',
    answer: 'Lack of time',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Lack of time|Lack of social support|Lack of energy|Lack of enjoyment',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which type of support is the most common provided by a fitness professional?',
    answer: 'Informational support',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Informational support|Emotional support|Instrumental support|Companionship support',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'This is a conversational technique that helps the listener express the supposed meaning of what was just heard.',
    answer: 'Reflections',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Reflections|Open-ended questions|Closed-ended questions|Active listening',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'At which stage of change are self-efficacy levels generally the highest?',
    answer: 'Maintenance',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Maintenance|Precontemplation|Contemplation|Preparation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'A client is asked to record what exercises they perform, how much they eat, and how much they sleep. Which of these strategies is the client using?',
    answer: 'Self-monitoring',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Self-monitoring|Imagery|Goal setting|Contemplation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'What stage of change is a person in if they are planning on exercising within the next 6 months?',
    answer: 'Contemplation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Contemplation|Action|Maintenance|Precontemplation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 2 Review',
    topic: 'Client Relations And Behavioral Coaching',
    question:
      'Which subtopic of psychology deals with how the environment affects exercise behavior?',
    answer: 'Sport and exercise psychology',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Sport and exercise psychology|Health psychology|Social psychology|Developmental psychology',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'What two factors are used to calculate body mass index (BMI)?',
    answer: 'Height and weight',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Height and weight|Weight and age|Height and age|Age and level of physical fitness',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Hypertension is categorized by a blood pressure greater than what measurement?',
    answer: '120/80 mm Hg',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: '120/80 mm Hg|120/60 mm Hg|125/75 mm Hg|80/120 mm Hg',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What is the blood pressure measurement that occurs when the heart is at rest or between beats?',
    answer: 'Diastolic blood pressure',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Diastolic blood pressure|Systolic blood pressure|Hypertension|Pulse',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      "At her first visit to her new fitness trainer, Alisha's BMI was 26. According to this information, how would Alisha be classified?",
    answer: 'Overweight',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Overweight|Obese|Healthy weight|Underweight',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What impacts can exercise have on cholesterol levels in the body?',
    answer: 'It can reduce LDL cholesterol and increase HDL cholesterol.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'It can reduce LDL cholesterol and increase HDL cholesterol.|It can increase LDL cholesterol.|It increases both HDL and LDL cholesterol.|It can lower both HDL and LDL cholesterol.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which section of the NASM Code of Professional Conduct requires that client records are disposed of in a secure manner?',
    answer: 'Confidentiality',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Confidentiality|Professionalism|Legal and ethical|Business practice',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What is the most appropriate way to conclude a sales presentation with a potential client?',
    answer: 'Asking for the sale and scheduling the first session',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Asking for the sale and scheduling the first session|Agreeing to call the potential client in 2 days to follow up|Swapping social media handles so the trainer and client can follow each other|Asking the member for a personal phone number to use to follow up via texting',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'Which of the following best defines cholesterol?',
    answer: 'A waxy, fatlike substance found in bodily cells',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A waxy, fatlike substance found in bodily cells|A substance that attaches itself to muscles and tendons|A narrowing of arteries to the heart|A raising of blood pressure',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      "Which term refers to a person's education, income, and occupation?",
    answer: 'Socioeconomic status',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Socioeconomic status|Behavioral health|Global state of health|Emotional health',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'According to the NASM Code of Professional Conduct, for how long must a fitness professional maintain accurate financial, contract, appointment, and tax records?',
    answer: '4 years',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: '4 years|1 year|6 months|Indefinitely',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What type of health concern is the leading cause of death in the world today?',
    answer: 'Chronic diseases and conditions',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Chronic diseases and conditions|Acute diseases|Injuries|Alcohol',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'What do the letters OPT within the OPT model stand for?',
    answer: 'Optimum Performance Training',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Optimum Performance Training|Optional Practical Training|Optional Performance Testing|Optimum Peak Teaching',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What is an important step after conducting an interview with a potential employer?',
    answer: 'Sending a handwritten thank-you letter or an email',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Sending a handwritten thank-you letter or an email|Posting a note on social media saying how much fun it was to interview and how cool it would be to work for the company|Having a parent call to ask about the interview results|Texting the hiring manager to thank them for their time during the interview',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Recently, what has become an effective way to deliver customized exercise solutions to clients based on their individual needs?',
    answer: 'Offering online coaching programs',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Offering online coaching programs|Teaching group fitness workouts|Offering customized meal plans for each client|Creating exercise programs to heal injured body parts',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'What statement best describes a premium health club?',
    answer:
      'A health club that features multiple group-fitness studio options and provides a selection of high-end amenities',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A health club that features multiple group-fitness studio options and provides a selection of high-end amenities|A health club that offers a low-price membership, often including very few amenities other than access to exercise equipment|A health club that uses revenue from fitness programs and memberships to cover operational costs, improve facilities, and fund a wide range of community-based initiatives|A private health club offered only at luxury resorts and golf courses',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Beth is considering opportunities for how to begin her career as a fitness professional. If her primary goal is to earn a stable income by helping clients reach their fitness goals, which of the following would provide the best option?',
    answer: 'Working for a premium health club company',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Working for a premium health club company|Working for a low-cost health club company|Offering in-home training services|Creating online coaching programs',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What is something that allows a fitness professional to stand out from others in featuring their services?',
    answer: 'Unique selling proposition (USP)',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Unique selling proposition (USP)|SWOT analysis|Statement of work (SOW)|PERT estimate',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Mac, an NASM-CPT, has been working as a personal trainer at a health club for almost 3 years. He has consistently received positive job evaluations, making him eligible for a promotion. What opportunity would be the most appropriate to pursue, given his experience?',
    answer: 'Fitness manager',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Fitness manager|General manager|Area fitness manager|Group fitness manager',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What is the best choice of attire to an interview at a health club?',
    answer: 'Professional business attire',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Professional business attire|Brand-new workout clothes|Jeans and a polo shirt|Business casual',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which of the following is not a component of an integrated approach to exercise?',
    answer: 'Diet supplementation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Diet supplementation|Balance|Speed, agility, and quickness|Core strength and stability',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Why is continued education required for NASM Certified Personal Trainers?',
    answer:
      'To ensure that fitness professionals stay current on the latest understandings and research findings within the industry',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "To ensure that fitness professionals stay current on the latest understandings and research findings within the industry|To elevate the fitness professional's status and reputation within the fitness community|To promote economic prosperity for the fitness industry and certifying organizations|To abide by federal guidelines that require continuing education units for allied health professionals",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'How can health best be defined?',
    answer:
      'A state of complete physical, mental, and social well-being, and not merely the absence of disease or infirmity',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A state of complete physical, mental, and social well-being, and not merely the absence of disease or infirmity|Genetics, access to healthcare, access to preventive medicine, socioeconomic status, natural disasters, and the built environment|A process by which the human body continually strives to maintain a relatively stable equilibrium in relation to the surrounding environment and the regular tasks it is required to perform|A combination of education, income, and occupation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'During an interview with the hiring manager at a large health club, Sarah, an NASM Certified Personal Trainer, is asked how she can contribute as a personal trainer even though she has no formal experience working in the field. What would be the most appropriate response?',
    answer:
      'Sarah discusses her previous work experience in a busy day care, where she had to multitask multiple times a day to perform her job duties. She thinks the multitasking helped prepare her for the demands of a busy fitness floor.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Sarah discusses her previous work experience in a busy day care, where she had to multitask multiple times a day to perform her job duties. She thinks the multitasking helped prepare her for the demands of a busy fitness floor.|Sarah discusses her experience as a high school athlete. Because she was a good athlete, she thinks she will be a good personal trainer.|Sarah mentions her experience training for figure competitions. She thinks that experience means that she can help clients train for their competitions.|Sarah mentions her experience as a cashier at a snack bar. She thinks this demonstrates her ability to run a cash register and complete daily cash reports.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'What is homeostasis?',
    answer:
      'A process by which the human body continually strives to maintain a relatively stable equilibrium',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A process by which the human body continually strives to maintain a relatively stable equilibrium\n' +
      '|Any abnormal condition that negatively affects the structure or function of a part of the body\n' +
      '|A combination of influences that include education, income, and occupation\n' +
      '|A situation in which the human body is rapidly changing all the time\n' +
      '',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What term describes the process of building a relationship based on communication and trust?',
    answer: 'Building rapport',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Building rapport|Working the floor|Forecasting|Developing a unique selling proposition (USP)',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Maria is interviewing for her first job as a fitness professional at a boutique fitness studio. Which previous experience would she want to make sure to discuss during the interview to demonstrate qualities of a Certified Personal Trainer?',
    answer:
      'Maria was repeatedly recognized as a top salesperson at the clothing store where she has been working.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Maria was repeatedly recognized as a top salesperson at the clothing store where she has been working.|Maria placed second in her first bikini competition.|Maria was a co-captain on a state champion volleyball team in high school.|Maria worked as a camp counselor at a youth sports camp while in college.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which statement best describes the final stage of the sales process?',
    answer:
      "Making the sale by asking for a financial commitment to solving the customer's needs",
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "Making the sale by asking for a financial commitment to solving the customer's needs|Identifying a customer's needs|Asking for referrals|Communicating solutions for the customer's needs",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Using the healthcare continuum, how would training with a fitness professional be classified?',
    answer: 'Preventive care',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Preventive care|Alternative medicine|Behavioral health|Physical therapy',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Jessica is looking to grow in her career as a personal trainer. Which employment option would offer her the best chance to provide mentorship to fitness professionals, use managerial skills, and respond directly to member needs when necessary?',
    answer: 'Fitness manager',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Fitness manager|General manager|Strength and conditioning coach|Master instructor',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which of the following best demonstrates an example of exercise?',
    answer: 'Weightlifting',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Weightlifting|Shoveling snow|Walking a dog|Yardwork',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What is the dysfunction that occurs due to narrowing and rubbing of the soft tissue and bony structures of the shoulder?',
    answer: 'Shoulder impingement',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Shoulder impingement|Rotator cuff tear|Frozen shoulder|Dislocation of the shoulder',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'How often does an NASM Certified Personal Trainer need to renew their certification?',
    answer: 'Every 2 years',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Every 2 years|Every year|Every 3 years|Every 5 years',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What statement best describes the main benefit for establishing a brand identity?',
    answer: 'A brand identity establishes a top-of-mind presence.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A brand identity establishes a top-of-mind presence.|A brand identity allows a fitness professional to design a colorful logo that attracts attention.|A brand identity provides more opportunities for being featured in magazines.|A brand identity could make it easier to create a social media profile.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'What statement best describes a low-cost health club?',
    answer:
      'A health club that offers a low-price membership, often including very few amenities other than access to exercise equipment',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A health club that offers a low-price membership, often including very few amenities other than access to exercise equipment|A health club that provides amenities like locker rooms, snack and supplement sales, and group fitness workouts included in the price of membership|A health club that features multiple group-fitness studio options and provides a selection of high-end amenities like towels and complimentary personal hygiene products, cafes, pools, sports courts, and childcare services|A health club that uses revenue from fitness programs and memberships to cover operational costs, improve facilities, and fund a wide range of community-based initiatives',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      "Which statement about a Certified Personal Trainer's scope of practice is accurate?",
    answer:
      'Certified Personal Trainers do not diagnose or treat areas of pain or disease.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Certified Personal Trainers do not diagnose or treat areas of pain or disease.|Certified Personal Trainers have specific governmental regulations that define their scope of practice.|The scope of practice for Certified Personal Trainers is consistent globally.|Once certified, a personal trainer is bound by law in the United States to a specific scope of practice.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Why can personal trainers be considered among the most important employees within a health club?',
    answer:
      'Personal trainers come in direct contact with members and can have the greatest influence on whether members achieve results.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Personal trainers come in direct contact with members and can have the greatest influence on whether members achieve results.|Personal trainers are often in great physical shape, which demonstrates that belonging to a health club can produce results members want.|Personal trainers are very outgoing and can help create a fun atmosphere in a fitness facility.|Personal trainers study exercise science and have the knowledge to help members get results.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'In a SWOT analysis, which of the following would be an example of a strength?',
    answer: 'Having the NASM-CPT credential',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Having the NASM-CPT credential|Taking a workshop to learn more about sales and marketing for fitness professionals|Needing to learn more about marketing and sales|Competition from the other health clubs and training studios in the immediate area',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'Which activity best demonstrates evidence-based practice?',
    answer: 'Referencing peer-reviewed research',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "Referencing peer-reviewed research|Referring to a colleague's practical knowledge|Referencing a social media post|Reading information presented in a blog article",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which chronic disease is the leading cause of death in the world today?',
    answer: 'Coronary artery disease',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Coronary artery disease|Cancer|Diabetes|Dementia',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'How many pages are most appropriate for a resume?',
    answer: 'One to two pages',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'One to two pages|Two to three pages|Three to four pages|One page only',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What is the purpose of a professional personal training certification?',
    answer:
      'To ensure that individual job candidates can demonstrate the ability to perform the tasks required for this job category',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'To ensure that individual job candidates can demonstrate the ability to perform the tasks required for this job category|To demonstrate that an individual is committed to the field of personal training|To abide by federal guidelines that require certification for fitness professionals|To ensure gyms and health clubs follow rules established by OSHA',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'What is a prospect?',
    answer: 'An individual who has been identified as a potential client',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'An individual who has been identified as a potential client|A business management technique that helps predict how much work is needed to meet a revenue goal|A potential career advancement opportunity|A method of creating a service identified by specific characteristics',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'Which individual is suffering from an acute disease?',
    answer: 'Jorge, who is sick with the flu',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Jorge, who is sick with the flu|Tricia, who has type 1 diabetes|Perry, who suffers from a congenital heart condition|Roger, who has type 2 diabetes',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What percentage of adults experience low-back pain at least once in their lifetime?',
    answer: '80%',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: '80%|50%|30%|90%',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'What are the basic two types of disease?',
    answer: 'Chronic and acute',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Chronic and acute|Chronic and not contagious|Acute and contagious|Chronic and noncommunicable',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'An anterior cruciate ligament (ACL) tear is a common injury to what part of the body?',
    answer: 'Knee',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Knee|Shoulder|Lumbo-pelvic-hip complex|Ankle',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which statement best describes the second stage of the sales process?',
    answer: "Communicating solutions for the customer's needs",
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "Communicating solutions for the customer's needs|Discussing the customer's budget|Discussing discounts on various personal training packages|Communicating the negative side effects of a sedentary lifestyle",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Identify the correct number of continuing education units (CEUs) that an NASM Certified Personal Trainer needs to complete in a 2-year cycle to renew the certification.',
    answer: '2',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: '2|1.5|3|4.5',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'Which condition is an example of a chronic disease?',
    answer: 'Type 2 diabetes',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Type 2 diabetes\n|Flu\n|Strep throat\n|Appendicitis\n',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'What statement best describes a nonprofit health club?',
    answer:
      'A health club that uses revenue from fitness programs and memberships to cover operational costs, improve facilities, and fund a wide range of community-based initiatives',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A health club that uses revenue from fitness programs and memberships to cover operational costs, improve facilities, and fund a wide range of community-based initiatives|A health club that offers a low-price membership, often including very few amenities other than access to exercise equipment|A health club that features multiple group-fitness studio options and provides a selection of high-end amenities like towels and complimentary personal hygiene products, cafes, pools, sports courts, and childcare services|A health club that offers complimentary memberships and free childcare services for low-income families',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which of the following best demonstrates an example of activities of daily living separate from planned exercise?',
    answer: 'Yardwork',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Yardwork|Cycling|Weightlifting|Running',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Rather than simply designing workout programs to change appearance, the modern personal trainer has evolved to a professional responsible for producing which of the following?',
    answer: 'Improving overall health and movement quality for their clients',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Improving overall health and movement quality for their clients|Designing meal plans that can help clients shed unwanted fat|Helping clients get shredded to stand out and gain more followers on social media|Creating exercise programs to heal injured body parts',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'Which of the following is true about cholesterol?',
    answer: 'Exercise has been shown to help reduce high cholesterol.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "Exercise has been shown to help reduce high cholesterol.|One can live without cholesterol.|Cholesterol is found only in the body's major organs.|For the body to produce enough cholesterol for daily needs, the diet must be supplemented with vitamins and minerals.",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'When working in a health club, what piece of equipment would it be essential to know the location of?',
    answer:
      'The AED, in case the personal trainer will need to perform CPR on a health club member',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The AED, in case the personal trainer will need to perform CPR on a health club member|The vacuum cleaner, in case a personal trainer has to clean during the shift|The remote control for the TVs or sound system|Rags and cleaning supplies',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which type of cholesterol tends to increase the risk of cardiovascular disease?',
    answer: 'LDL (low-density lipoprotein)',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'LDL (low-density lipoprotein)|HDL (high-density lipoprotein)|EDL (elevated-density lipoprotein)|MDL (medium-density lipoprotein)',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What is a professional development technique that helps individuals identify their personal strengths and weaknesses, opportunities for growth, and potential threats to success?',
    answer: 'A SWOT analysis',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A SWOT analysis|A unique selling proposition (USP)|Forecasting|Building rapport',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Dan, an NASM Certified Personal Trainer, completed what he felt was a very successful interview with the hiring manager at a top fitness studio. What is the best course of action if Dan is interested in moving on to the next phase of the interview process?',
    answer:
      'Writing a handwritten note to thank the hiring manager for the opportunity to interview for the job',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Writing a handwritten note to thank the hiring manager for the opportunity to interview for the job|Sending a text to the manager saying, “Thanks for your time.”|Calling the manager to ask when the first day of work will be scheduled|Posting a video on social media showing him working out at the health club',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'For a Certified Personal Trainer, what would provide the most time-efficient option for increasing income potential?',
    answer: 'Learning how to lead group training programs',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Learning how to lead group training programs|Pursuing a degree in exercise science|Becoming a registered dietitian nutritionist (RDN) to provide nutritional counseling|Earning a massage therapy license to be able to offer massage treatments',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What condition is characterized by the narrowing of coronary arteries?',
    answer: 'Ischemic heart disease',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Ischemic heart disease|Arrhythmia|Heart valve problem|Hypertension',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'Which common cause of death is the most preventable?',
    answer: 'Obesity',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Obesity|Cancer|Stroke|Dementia',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'How many CEUs does the mandatory CPR/AED certification provide for renewal of the NASM-CPT credential?',
    answer: '0.1',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: '0.1|0.2|1|0.5',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Why is it important for fitness professionals to pay attention to their personal grooming when working in a fitness facility?',
    answer:
      'Personal trainers are professionals. Having a professional appearance can help ensure that clients treat personal trainers as the professionals they are.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Personal trainers are professionals. Having a professional appearance can help ensure that clients treat personal trainers as the professionals they are.|Paying attention to personal grooming will make it easier to make new friends while working.|Personal grooming is critical for creating engaging social media posts.|Personal grooming can help personal trainers appear more in shape, which is important for attracting clients.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'Which statement about lowering blood pressure is true?',
    answer:
      'Planned exercise alone is typically insufficient for acutely lowering and controlling hypertension.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Planned exercise alone is typically insufficient for acutely lowering and controlling hypertension.|Exercise can help control body weight, but it cannot improve blood flow.|Reducing excessive alcohol use will not have an impact on high blood pressure.|There is no direct evidence that exercise will result in lower blood pressure.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Roberta is an NASM Certified Personal Trainer who is going to be working as an independent contractor at a popular health club. What is the most important step to take before starting her job?',
    answer: 'Purchasing liability insurance to protect her personal assets',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Purchasing liability insurance to protect her personal assets|Purchasing social media followers to enhance her profile|Designing cute T-shirts with her logo to give away to potential clients|Buying new outfits so that other members will notice her while she’s working out',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which statement best describes the first stage of the sales process?',
    answer: "Identifying a customer's needs",
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "Identifying a customer's needs|Discussing pricing options|Asking for referrals|Promoting the benefits of personal training for improving health and longevity",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which of the following is a necessity for all fitness professionals to remain successful in the industry?',
    answer: 'Keeping up with the latest science and changes in the industry',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Keeping up with the latest science and changes in the industry|Annual certification by NASM|Having at least 15 active clients at all times|Occasional publishing in relevant journals',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Prior to ever working with a client, what is the most important priority when starting an independent personal training business?',
    answer: 'Purchasing liability insurance and appropriate business licenses',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Purchasing liability insurance and appropriate business licenses|Having consistent names on all social media accounts|Purchasing fitness equipment|Designing a website to advertise personal training services',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'At her annual physical, Claire found out her blood pressure was 110/70 mm Hg. According to this information, which statement is true?',
    answer: 'Her diastolic pressure is 70.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Her diastolic pressure is 70.|Her systolic pressure is 70.|She has hypertension.|She needs to modify her diet to bring down her blood pressure.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Robert is a recently retired military veteran. He has earned his NASM-CPT credential because he wants to help young people prepare for the physical demands of serving in the military. Which employment options provide him with the greatest access to potential clients in all geographic locations?',
    answer: 'Conducting online coaching and personal training',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Conducting online coaching and personal training|Working in a nonprofit facility|Hosting boot camps in a local park|Working as an in-home independent personal trainer',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'What is forecasting?',
    answer:
      'A business management technique that helps predict how much work is needed to meet a revenue goal',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A business management technique that helps predict how much work is needed to meet a revenue goal|A relationship in which two people understand each other’s ideas, have respect for one another, and communicate well|A rapport-building technique where fitness professionals walk around the gym floor talking to members without overtly presenting a sale|A system for learning about the needs of a potential client to be able to identify and present a number of solutions for those needs',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which component of evidence-based practice refers to a fitness professional’s accumulated education, experience, and practical skills?',
    answer: 'Individual professional expertise',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Individual professional expertise|Best external evidence|Client values and expectations|Number of continuing education units earned',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Karim, an NASM Certified Personal Trainer, recently retired from playing professional football and is beginning his career in the fitness industry. How can Karim best promote his experience as a professional athlete?',
    answer:
      'Karim’s experience as a professional athlete allows him to create a unique selling proposition (USP) allowing club members to exercise with a former professional athlete.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Karim’s experience as a professional athlete allows him to create a unique selling proposition (USP) allowing club members to exercise with a former professional athlete.|Karim’s experience as a professional athlete allows him to establish immediate rapport with club members and potential clients.|Karim’s experience as a professional athlete allows him to establish a recognizable brand identity.|Karim’s experience as a professional athlete gives him the ability to create an accurate business forecast.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'What most correctly identifies the purpose of a resume?',
    answer:
      'A resume allows a job candidate to present their job skills to a potential employer.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A resume allows a job candidate to present their job skills to a potential employer.|A resume allows a job candidate to highlight their expertise in a particular field.|A resume allows a job candidate to express a personal statement about their passion.|A resume allows a job candidate to identify athletic accomplishments.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What are two of the most common issues at the foot and ankle complex?',
    answer: 'Sprains and plantar fasciitis',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "Sprains and plantar fasciitis|Strains and heel spurs|Plantar fasciitis and shin splints|Achilles tendonitis and athlete's foot",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'Which of the following is unique to type 2 diabetes?',
    answer: 'Insulin resistance',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Insulin resistance|The body has low levels of insulin.|The pancreas does not make insulin.|It can develop regardless of a healthy diet.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'How are open-ended questions best used during the sales process?',
    answer:
      "The questions identify the customer's wants, needs, fears, and desires.",
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "The questions identify the customer's wants, needs, fears, and desires.|The questions are easy for the customer to answer, as they can be answered with a simple yes or no.|The questions help a personal trainer learn about a customer's family medical history.|The questions help a personal trainer learn if the customer's workout schedule fits within the personal trainer's availability.",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'When NASM recommends relying on the current best information in making decisions about client care, what is it referring to?',
    answer: 'Evidence-based practice',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Evidence-based practice|Traditional compliance|Peer-observed procedure|Popular theories and methods posted on online fitness forums',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'How can fitness professionals earn CEUs?',
    answer: 'Attending fitness industry conferences',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Attending fitness industry conferences|Reading scholarly research journals|Accumulating hours training clients either independently or in a health club|Reading exercise-science textbooks',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'What are the three levels of the OPT model?',
    answer: 'Stabilization, strength, and power',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Stabilization, strength, and power|Diet, exercise, and recovery|Health, fitness, and wellness|Flexibility, cardiorespiratory, and resistance',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which statement about chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD) is accurate?',
    answer: 'It is not a curable disease.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'It is not a curable disease.|Brisk walking is not recommended, as it can bring on symptoms.|It is an acute disease.|It is typically a stress-induced condition.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What marketing strategy would be most effective at helping a fitness professional tell a story and create an instantly recognizable level of service?',
    answer: 'Creating a brand identity',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Creating a brand identity|Offering free T-shirts|Providing complimentary water bottles|Advertising sales and discounts',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'What is the main role of a personal trainer?',
    answer:
      'Assess clients and make recommendations for exercise programming and other lifestyle changes',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Assess clients and make recommendations for exercise programming and other lifestyle changes|Teach, lead, and motivate individuals through large-group exercise classes|Provide advanced strength and conditioning programs for competitive athletes|Provide nutritional advice, therapy, and counseling to a wide range of clients',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'The human body is uniquely designed to respond to stress and, if necessary, make changes to maintain optimal health and physiological functioning. What is this process called?',
    answer: 'Homeostasis',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Homeostasis|Fight-or-flight response|Neuromuscular efficiency|Excitation-contraction coupling',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which section of the NASM Code of Professional Conduct requires the use of appropriate professional communication in all verbal, nonverbal, and written transactions?',
    answer: 'Professionalism',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Professionalism|Confidentiality|Legal and ethical|Business practice',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      "At his first visit to his new fitness trainer, Robert's BMI was 37. According to this information, how would Robert be classified?",
    answer: 'Obese',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Obese|Overweight|Healthy weight|Underweight',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'What statement best describes a mid-market health club?',
    answer:
      'A health club that provides all the features of low-cost clubs and additional amenities like higher-end locker rooms, snack and supplement sales, and group fitness workouts included in the price of membership',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A health club that provides all the features of low-cost clubs and additional amenities like higher-end locker rooms, snack and supplement sales, and group fitness workouts included in the price of membership|A health club that uses revenue from fitness programs and memberships to cover operational costs, improve facilities, and fund a wide range of community-based initiatives|A health club that features multiple group-fitness studio options and provides a selection of high-end amenities like towels and complimentary personal hygiene products, cafes, pools, sports courts, and childcare services|A health club that offers a low-price membership, often including very few amenities other than access to exercise equipment',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What is the most effective way to learn more about a large health club company before an interview with a hiring manager?',
    answer:
      'Reviewing the company website and social media channels to learn about all the programs and services offered',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Reviewing the company website and social media channels to learn about all the programs and services offered|Reading the reviews of the company and its programs on ratings websites|Following the most popular instructors from the club on social media|Visiting the club to ask members what they think about their experience at the club',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Roderick, an NASM-CPT, has submitted his application to be a personal trainer through the website of a large health club company. What will provide the best opportunity to get noticed by the hiring manager?',
    answer:
      'Wearing a suit and tie to the health club to drop off a resume with the hiring manager and complete an application in person',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Wearing a suit and tie to the health club to drop off a resume with the hiring manager and complete an application in person|Showing up at the club in workout clothes, explaining that he is an applicant, and asking for a free workout|Posting workout videos to a social media account and tagging the health club and hiring managers|Calling the health club, asking to speak to the hiring manager, and explaining he is perfect for the job',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'Which statement about cancer is most accurate?',
    answer: 'Cells in the body grow abnormally.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Cells in the body grow abnormally.|There is a lack of cell growth in the body.|It is most common in adults between the ages of 30 and 55.|Almost all cancers are preventable.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which term best describes a class of chronic respiratory dysfunctions that are characterized by increased breathlessness, airflow limitation, and accelerated decline of lung function?',
    answer: 'Chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD)',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD)|Asthma|Hypertension|Lung cancer',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which of the following answers indicates a primary difference between working as an independent contractor and working as an employee?',
    answer:
      'An independent contractor is responsible for paying their own taxes, while an employee has taxes withheld by the employer.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'An independent contractor is responsible for paying their own taxes, while an employee has taxes withheld by the employer.|An employee can establish their own hours, while an independent contractor must adhere to a specific work schedule.|An employee can earn more per hour than an independent contractor.|An independent contractor can expect client referrals from a facility, while an employee will have to find clients on the gym floor.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question: 'Which of the following is not a negative side effect of stress?',
    answer: 'The release of endorphins',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The release of endorphins|Atherosclerosis|Hypertension|Restricted blood flow',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Bridget, an NASM Certified Personal Trainer, is looking for ways to satisfy her CEU requirement. Which of the following would be an accepted means to fulfill this requirement?',
    answer:
      'Completing an NASM specialization worth 1.9 CEUs, along with a CPR/AED course for 0.1 CEUs',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Completing an NASM specialization worth 1.9 CEUs, along with a CPR/AED course for 0.1 CEUs|Attending an 8-hour fitness seminar|Reading a textbook on a related fitness topic|Completing an approved CEU course for 0.9 CEUs, along with the CPR/AED for 0.1 CEUs',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'With type 1 diabetes, what hormone does the pancreas fall short in making?',
    answer: 'Insulin',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Insulin|Testosterone|Estrogen|Progesterone',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What group of hormones are released by the brain during exercise help reduce pain?',
    answer: 'Endorphins',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Endorphins|Androgens|Adrenaline|Melatonin',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Javier has recently earned his NASM Certified Personal Trainer credential and is starting to apply to health clubs for his first job as a personal trainer. Which job from his previous non-fitness industry work experience demonstrates qualities that would best be applicable to personal training?',
    answer: 'Restaurant server',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Restaurant server|Nightclub security guard|Warehouse worker|Driver for a ride-sharing service',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Before studying to become an NASM Certified Personal Trainer, Kim worked as a copywriter for a large ad agency. Now that she is working as a personal trainer at a fitness studio, she is looking for additional income opportunities. Which of the following would provide her with the best option for increasing her earning potential?',
    answer:
      'Marketing her services as a writer to create blogs and social media posts for her studio as well as other fitness professionals in her area',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Marketing her services as a writer to create blogs and social media posts for her studio as well as other fitness professionals in her area|Becoming an NASM Master Instructor|College football conditioning coach|College instructor',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'Which of the following injuries is characterized by a sharp pain in the bottom of the heel that makes it difficult to walk?',
    answer: 'Plantar fasciitis',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Plantar fasciitis|A sprain|Patellar tendonitis|Anterior cruciate ligament (ACL) tear',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 1 Review',
    topic: 'Professional Development And Responsibility',
    question:
      'What type of fitness professional has advanced knowledge, training, and experience in designing and implementing strength and conditioning programs for competitive athletes?',
    answer: 'Strength and conditioning coach',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Strength and conditioning coach|Group fitness instructor|Certified Personal Trainer|Physical therapist',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'What does the first law of thermodynamics state?',
    answer: 'Energy can neither be created nor destroyed.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Energy can neither be created nor destroyed.|All energy is converted to heat.|Food increases metabolic rate.|Metabolic rate is constant.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'What is stroke volume?',
    answer: 'The amount of blood pumped out of the heart with each contraction',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The amount of blood pumped out of the heart with each contraction|The amount of blood pumped by the heart per minute|The amount of blood in the ventricle before contraction|The amount of blood remaining in the ventricle after contraction',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Omega-3 fatty acids do not include which of the following fatty acids?',
    answer: 'Palmitic acid',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Palmitic acid|Eicosapentaenoic acid (EPA)|Docosahexaenoic acid (DHA)|Alpha-linolenic acid (ALA)',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Which component contributes the most to total energy expenditure?',
    answer: 'Resting metabolism',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Resting metabolism|Thermic effect of food|Thermic effect of activity|Exercise',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'What is credible nutrition information?',
    answer: 'Nutrition information that is rooted in and supported by science',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Nutrition information that is rooted in and supported by science|Nutrition information that is supported by news and media|Nutrition information that is believable|Nutrition information that is reported to be true',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'If someone specifically wanted to burn a lot of fat (not necessarily total calories), what type of exercise should they do?',
    answer: 'Low- to moderate-intensity exercise for 30 to 60 minutes',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Low- to moderate-intensity exercise for 30 to 60 minutes|High-intensity exercise for less than 10 minutes|Walking for 5 minutes|High-intensity exercise for 10 to 15 minutes',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'What is the scientific term that describes the nervous system’s role in the contract/relax relationship between agonists and antagonists?',
    answer: 'Reciprocal inhibition',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Reciprocal inhibition|Muscle imbalance|Length-tension relationship|Stretch-shortening cycle',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Approximately what percentage of the human body (in male and female adults) is comprised of water?',
    answer: '0.6',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: '0.6|0.5|0.8|0.4',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'What is it called when a ligament is overstretched or torn?',
    answer: 'A sprain',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'A sprain|A strain|A twist|A pull',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Which heart chamber receives deoxygenated blood and pumps it to the lungs?',
    answer: 'Right ventricle',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Right ventricle|Left ventricle|Left atrium|Right atrium',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'Which of the following is the functional unit of a muscle cell?',
    answer: 'A sarcomere',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'A sarcomere|Actin|Myosin|Endomysium',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'What is the name for projections protruding from the bone to which tendons and ligaments attach?',
    answer: 'Processes',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Processes|Bone spurs|Depressions|Sulcus',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Which of the following nutrition topics are within the scope of practice for a Certified Personal Trainer?',
    answer:
      'General guidance on the importance of nutrition for health and performance',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'General guidance on the importance of nutrition for health and performance|Specific nutrition recommendations for an individual’s caloric, macronutrient, or micronutrient intake|Medical nutrition therapy as related to an individual’s medical diagnoses|Meal planning with caloric or nutrient-specific guidelines for weight loss/gain or sports performance',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'What is the primary purpose of the peripheral nervous system?',
    answer: 'To connect the central nervous system to the rest of the body',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'To connect the central nervous system to the rest of the body|To coordinate the activity of all parts of the body|To transmit impulses between afferent and efferent neurons|To transmit nervous impulses from neuron to neuron',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Which of the following conditions would produce nutritional ketosis in the body?',
    answer: 'A very low-carbohydrate diet',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A very low-carbohydrate diet|High-intensity exercise|A caloric surplus|A low-protein diet',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'How can basal metabolic rate (BMR) best be defined?',
    answer: 'The amount of energy required to maintain the body at rest',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "The amount of energy required to maintain the body at rest|An anabolic hormone produced by the liver, which is responsible for growth and development|A method to help determine an individual's heart rate|The amount of energy required to maintain the body when active",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Which of the following would be a credible source of nutrition information?',
    answer: 'The Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics|The Washington Post|A newspaper review article|Social media',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Which of the following effects of the cardiovascular system occurs during exercise?',
    answer: 'Increased ventricular filling',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Increased ventricular filling|Decreased venous return|Venous pooling|Decreased ventricular filling',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'What breathing change occurs at the second ventilatory threshold (VT2)?',
    answer: 'Expiration becomes more forceful.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Expiration becomes more forceful.|Breathing settles into a more consistent rhythm.|Inspiration is prolonged.|Breathing becomes more shallow.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Which governmental agency regulates dietary supplements in Australia?',
    answer: 'Therapeutic Goods Administration (TGA)',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Therapeutic Goods Administration (TGA)|Food and Drug Administration (FDA)|World Anti-Doping Agency (WADA)|Health Canada',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Which governmental agency regulates dietary supplements in the United States?',
    answer: 'Food and Drug Administration (FDA)',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Food and Drug Administration (FDA)|Therapeutic Goods Administration (TGA)|European Food Safety Authority (EFSA)|World Anti-Doping Agency (WADA)',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Which substrate provides nearly all the energy for activity at and above VT2?',
    answer: 'Glucose',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Glucose|Fat|Protein|Ketone bodies',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'The pathway for hormones secreted by the endocrine system may be described by which of the following?',
    answer:
      'The gland secretes the hormone, which travels through the bloodstream to reach a target cell, where it binds to a receptor and influences a particular action.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The gland secretes the hormone, which travels through the bloodstream to reach a target cell, where it binds to a receptor and influences a particular action.|The gland secretes the hormone, which bypasses the bloodstream and binds to a receptor on the target cell to exert a particular action.|The target cell releases the hormone, which travels through the bloodstream to the gland to exert a particular action.|The hormone is secreted by the bloodstream and travels to the gland to exert a particular effect.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Which of the following muscles is primarily targeted when performing a biceps curl exercise with the thumb up?',
    answer: 'Brachioradialis',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Brachioradialis|Biceps brachii|Triceps brachii|Brachialis',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'When ADP is converted to ATP, what is this process called?',
    answer: 'Phosphorylation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Phosphorylation|Oxidation|Transformation|ATP-PC',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'Which system is comprised of the airways and lungs?',
    answer: 'Respiratory',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Respiratory|Cardiovascular|Digestive|Endocrine',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'What is the bone type of the clavicle, radius, and ulna?',
    answer: 'Long',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Long|Irregular|Short|Flat',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Which type of lipids are considered to be heart-healthy and associated with reduced inflammation?',
    answer: 'Omega-3 fatty acids',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Omega-3 fatty acids\n' +
      '|Omega-6 fatty acids\n' +
      '|Trans fats\n' +
      '|Saturated fats\n' +
      '',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'What is the concept used to describe the action of muscles that have the ability to contract automatically in anticipation of movement?',
    answer: 'Feed-forward',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Feed-forward|Antagonist function|Synergist function|Feedback',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'What is the process by which bone is constantly renewed?',
    answer: 'Remodeling',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: "Remodeling|Wolff's law|Osteoporosis|Neuroplasticity",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Which subsystem is responsible for providing both frontal plane mobility and stabilization of the lumbo-pelvic-hip complex?',
    answer: 'Lateral subsystem',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Lateral subsystem|Deep longitudinal subsystem|Posterior oblique subsystem|Anterior oblique subsystem',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'What is adaptive thermogenesis?',
    answer:
      'Metabolic adaptations and changes in energy expenditure due to changes in energy intake',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Metabolic adaptations and changes in energy expenditure due to changes in energy intake|Increased heat production due to changes in energy expenditure|Changes in energy intake due to changes in energy expenditure|Adaptations to exercise due to changes in energy intake',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'What are the three branched chain amino acids (BCAAs)?',
    answer: 'Valine, leucine, and isoleucine',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Valine, leucine, and isoleucine|Histidine, threonine, and phenylalanine|Alanine, glutamine, and tyrosine|Methionine, tryptophan, and lysine',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'What answer best describes the building blocks of proteins?',
    answer: 'Essential and nonessential amino acids',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Essential and nonessential amino acids|Peptide bonds|Essential amino acids only|Carbon molecules',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'What is the primary function of the large intestine?',
    answer: 'Absorption of food and passage of waste into the rectum',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Absorption of food and passage of waste into the rectum|Digestion of food and passage of waste into the small intestine|Digestion of food and passage of waste into the rectum|Absorption of food and passage of waste into the small intestine',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'A client reports that he was recently told by his doctor that he has high blood sugar and that he should try to reduce it through dietary changes before considering medication. He asks you for advice. What would be the most appropriate course of action?',
    answer:
      'Explain that medical nutrition therapy is outside your scope of practice, then refer him to a registered dietitian for nutrition counseling.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Explain that medical nutrition therapy is outside your scope of practice, then refer him to a registered dietitian for nutrition counseling.|Say that you cannot help him because this is a medical issue, and tell him he needs to follow up with his doctor again.|Agree to review his diet and provide him with specific dietary guidelines on what foods to eat and what to avoid.|Give him a diabetic meal plan that you find on the internet.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'What are the three micronutrients?',
    answer: 'Vitamins, minerals, and phytonutrients',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Vitamins, minerals, and phytonutrients|Protein, carbohydrates, and lipids|Protein, carbohydrates, and fluids|Vitamins, minerals, and lipids',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'During a squat, which muscle group isometrically contracts to prevent unnecessary thigh movement in the frontal plane?',
    answer: 'Hip abductors',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Hip abductors|Hip flexors|Hip extensors|Hip internal rotators',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Which of the following would occur during intermittent exercise?',
    answer:
      'All three energy systems would be used at some point during the activity.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'All three energy systems would be used at some point during the activity.|A steady-state intensity would be used.|Fat would be the main energy source.|Carbohydrates would not be a major energy source.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Vitamin K supplements should be avoided by those taking which type of medication?',
    answer: 'Anticoagulants (e.g., warfarin)',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Anticoagulants (e.g., warfarin)|Painkillers|Inhalers|Insulin',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'What is the acceptable macronutrient distribution range (AMDR) for carbohydrate in the diet?',
    answer: '45 to 65% of total calories',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      '45 to 65% of total calories\n' +
      '|30 to 50% of total calories\n' +
      '|20 to 35% of total calories\n' +
      '|10 to 35% of total calories\n' +
      '',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'The process of diffusion of oxygen and carbon dioxide gases in and out of the bloodstream occurs in what structure or structures?',
    answer: 'Alveolar sacs',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Alveolar sacs|Trachea|Bronchioles|Pulmonary arteries',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'Which feature of a food label would enable a client to assess the nutrient composition of a food product?',
    answer: 'The nutrition facts panel',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The nutrition facts panel|The ingredients list|The percent reference intake|The nutrient-to-ingredient ratio',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'What is the term for the chemical messengers that cross the synapse between the neuron and muscle and assist with nerve transmission?',
    answer: 'Neurotransmitters',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Neurotransmitters|Synapses|Sarcomeres|Adenosine triphosphate',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'What would be considered a normal resting heart rate for a healthy sedentary person?',
    answer: '80 beats per minute',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      '80 beats per minute|120 beats per minute|50 beats per minute|105 beats per minute',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'What effect would sleep deprivation have on growth hormone and cortisol levels?',
    answer:
      'Inadequate sleep will decrease growth hormone and increase cortisol levels.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Inadequate sleep will decrease growth hormone and increase cortisol levels.|Inadequate sleep will increase growth hormone and cortisol levels.|Inadequate sleep will decrease growth hormone and cortisol levels.|Inadequate sleep will increase growth hormone levels and decrease cortisol levels.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question: 'The water-soluble vitamins include which vitamins?',
    answer: 'Vitamin C and the B complex vitamins',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Vitamin C and the B complex vitamins|Vitamin C, D, and K|Vitamin C, B complex, and D|Vitamin C, B complex, and K',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'You are working with a new client who recently started a low-carbohydrate diet for weight loss. However, she complains of being tired and lacking energy for her training sessions. What might be the reason for her low energy?',
    answer: 'Inadequate carbohydrate intake',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Inadequate carbohydrate intake|Inadequate protein intake|Inadequate fat intake|Excess fat intake',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      "When a gymnast balances on a beam, they are aware of their body's general orientation and the relative position of its parts. This is due to which key sensory function?",
    answer: 'Proprioception',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: "Proprioception|Stretch reflex|Neuroplasticity|Wolff's law",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 3 Review',
    topic: 'Basic And Applied Sciences And Nutritional Coaching',
    question:
      'At what age is the adolescent brain considered to be fully developed?',
    answer: '25',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: '25|30|18|22',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'What is explained by the sliding filament theory?',
    answer: 'The shortening of a sarcomere to produce a muscle contraction',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The shortening of a sarcomere to produce a muscle contraction|The lengthening of a sarcomere after a muscle contraction|The actin pulling the myosin toward the center of the sarcomere|The Z-lines moving farther apart',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'What is a characteristic of a type I muscle fiber?',
    answer: 'Less force production',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Less force production|Larger in size|Quick to fatigue|Fewer capillaries',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'Which system supplies neural input to organs that run the involuntary processes of the body?',
    answer: 'Autonomic nervous system',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Autonomic nervous system|Somatic nervous system|Mechanoreceptors|The brain',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'What activity is especially beneficial for combating the loss of muscle mass, power, and strength for aging adults?',
    answer: 'Resistance training',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Resistance training|Cardio|Aerobics|Walking',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'What are the two divisions of the skeletal system?',
    answer: 'Axial and appendicular',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Axial and appendicular|Upper and lower|Anterior and posterior|Osteoclasts and osteoblasts',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'What surrounds the skeletal muscles and connects them to other surrounding muscles?',
    answer: 'Fascia',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Fascia|Connective tissues|Tendons|Muscle spindles',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'Which joints are most associated with human movement?',
    answer: 'Synovial',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Synovial|Nonaxial|Saddle|Nonsynovial',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'At what age is total peak bone mass reached?',
    answer: '30',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: '30|18|25|35',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'Which joint has the simplest movement, moving either back and forth or side to side?',
    answer: 'Nonaxial',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Nonaxial|Synovial|Nonsynovial|Condyloid',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'Which mechanoreceptor is sensitive to changes in muscular tension and rate of that tension change, causing the muscle to relax, which prevents the muscle from excessive stress and possible injury?',
    answer: 'Golgi tendon organs',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Golgi tendon organs|Joint receptors|Muscle spindles|Interneurons',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'One of the two interdependent divisions of the nervous system is the central nervous system. What is the second division?',
    answer: 'Peripheral nervous system',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Peripheral nervous system|Autonomic nervous system|Somatic nervous system|Sympathetic nervous system',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'Which system puts the body into a relaxed state, termed rest and digest?',
    answer: 'Parasympathetic nervous system',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Parasympathetic nervous system|Sympathetic nervous system|Somatic nervous system|Central nervous system',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'Which term describes the movement of bones, such as flexion and extension?',
    answer: 'Osteokinematics',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Osteokinematics|Arthrokinematics|Osteoporosis|Arthropathy',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'What is the correct order of segments for the spine, starting at the top?',
    answer: 'Cervical, thoracic, and lumbar',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Cervical, thoracic, and lumbar|Thoracic, cervical, and lumbar|Cervical, lumbar, and thoracic|Lumbar, cervical, and thoracic',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'Which of the following protein structures is important for muscular contractions by providing a binding site?',
    answer: 'Troponin',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Troponin|Actin|Myosin|Fascicles',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'What are the two components of the central nervous system?',
    answer: 'The brain and spinal cord',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The brain and spinal cord|The nerves and sensory receptors|The somatic and autonomic nervous systems|The sympathetic and parasympathetic nervous systems',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'Which characteristic is exhibited by type I muscle fibers?',
    answer: 'Slow to fatigue',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Slow to fatigue|Decreased oxygen delivery|Short-term contractions|Fewer capillaries',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question: 'What advice would enable a client to breathe properly?',
    answer:
      'Sit upright and slowly breathe in through your nose while allowing your stomach to expand.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Sit upright and slowly breathe in through your nose while allowing your stomach to expand.|Sit upright and slowly breathe in through your mouth while allowing your chest to expand.|Sit with an increased kyphosis and slowly breathe in through your nose while allowing your stomach to expand.|Sit with an increased kyphosis and slowly breathe in through your nose while minimizing abdominal movement.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question: 'What is end-diastolic volume?',
    answer: 'The amount of blood in the ventricle before contraction',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The amount of blood in the ventricle before contraction|The volume of blood pumped by the heart per minute|The amount of blood pumped out of the heart with each contraction|The amount of blood remaining in the ventricle after contraction',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question: 'Where in the digestive system are most fluids absorbed?',
    answer: 'Small intestine',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Small intestine|Large intestine|Stomach|Esophagus',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question: 'What is the primary muscle type of the heart?',
    answer: 'Cardiac',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Cardiac|Skeletal|Smooth|Myofibril',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question:
      'What component of breathing improves blood flow back to the heart?',
    answer: 'Inspiration with a decrease in intrathoracic pressure',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Inspiration with a decrease in intrathoracic pressure|Inspiration with an increase in intrathoracic pressure|Expiration with an increase in intrathoracic pressure|Expiration with a decrease in intrathoracic pressure',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question:
      'Which of the following exercises would be most likely to contribute to an acute increase in testosterone levels?',
    answer: 'Back squat',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Back squat|Bench press|Triceps extension|Calf raise',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question:
      'Which heart chamber gathers deoxygenated blood returning to the heart from the superior and inferior vena cava veins?',
    answer: 'Right atrium',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Right atrium|Left atrium|Left ventricle|Right ventricle',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question:
      'Which of the following blood pressure values would be classified as normal according to the American Heart Association?',
    answer: 'Systolic <120 and diastolic <80',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Systolic <120 and diastolic <80|Systolic 120 to 129 and diastolic <80|Systolic 130 to 139 or diastolic 80 to 89|Systolic >180 and/or diastolic >120',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question: 'The pancreas secretes which of the following hormones?',
    answer: 'Insulin',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Insulin|Growth hormone|Testosterone|Insulin-like growth factor',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question: 'What is cardiac output?',
    answer: 'The volume of blood pumped by the heart per minute',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The volume of blood pumped by the heart per minute|The volume of blood pumped by the heart per beat or contraction|The amount of blood in the ventricle before contraction|The amount of blood remaining in the ventricle after contraction',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question:
      'The cardiovascular and respiratory systems work together to provide the body with what gas?',
    answer: 'Oxygen',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Oxygen|Carbon dioxide|Water|Platelets',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question:
      'What change would lead to an increase in cardiac output during exercise?',
    answer: 'Increased heart rate',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Increased heart rate|Decreased heart rate|Decreased stroke volume|Increased end-systolic volume',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question:
      'What scientific term is used to describe the concept whereby a loaded eccentric contraction prepares the muscles for a rapid concentric contraction?',
    answer: 'Stretch-shortening cycle',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Stretch-shortening cycle|Series elastic component|Reciprocal inhibition|Altered reciprocal inhibition',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question:
      'What is the anatomical term that describes something positioned on the opposite side of the body?',
    answer: 'Contralateral',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Contralateral|Ipsilateral|Lateral|Posterior',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question:
      'What measurement is dependent upon the length of the lever arm and the angle between the force application and the lever arm?',
    answer: 'Torque',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Torque|Force|Arthrokinematics|Force velocity',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question:
      'What type of lever could be described as having a fulcrum in the middle like a seesaw?',
    answer: 'First class',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'First class|Second class|Third class|Fourth class',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question: 'Pronation of the foot describes what multiplanar movements?',
    answer: 'Eversion, dorsiflexion, and ankle abduction',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Eversion, dorsiflexion, and ankle abduction|Inversion, dorsiflexion, and ankle adduction|Eversion, dorsiflexion, and ankle adduction|Eversion, plantar flexion, and ankle abduction',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question:
      'During normal walking, the pelvis rotates in what plane to facilitate the necessary momentum for the swing phase?',
    answer: 'Transverse',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Transverse|Axial|Sagittal|Frontal',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question:
      'Which of the following statements would be accurate with regard to muscle force and velocity during an eccentric muscle action?',
    answer:
      'As the contraction velocity increases the ability to develop force also increases.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'As the contraction velocity increases the ability to develop force also increases.|As the contraction velocity increases, the ability to develop force decreases.|As the contraction velocity decreases, the ability to develop force increases.|As the contraction velocity decreases, the force remains constant.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question:
      'Overactive hip flexors may lead to which of the following postural compensations?',
    answer: 'Anterior tilting of the pelvis and an increased low-back arch',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Anterior tilting of the pelvis and an increased low-back arch|Anterior tilting of the pelvis and a decreased low-back arch|Posterior tilting of the pelvis and an increased low-back arch|Posterior tilting of the pelvis and a decreased low-back arch',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question:
      'Which type of exercise accommodates effort whereby the harder the individual pushes or pulls, the more resistance they feel, despite the movement speed remaining constant?',
    answer: 'Isokinetic',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Isokinetic|Concentric|Eccentric|Isometric',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question: 'What is the most accurate description of motor control?',
    answer:
      'The ability to initiate and correct purposeful controlled movements',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The ability to initiate and correct purposeful controlled movements|The integration of motor control processes through practice|The cumulative changes in motor behavior over time, throughout the life span|The motor response to internal and external environmental stimuli',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question:
      'What is the anatomical term that describes something positioned above an identified reference point?',
    answer: 'Superior',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Superior|Inferior|Anterior|Posterior',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question:
      'Which of the following muscle groups work both eccentrically and concentrically in the sagittal plane during a squat?',
    answer: 'Quadriceps',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Quadriceps|Adductor longus|Gluteus medius|Biceps brachii',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question:
      'Movements that take place within a joint and are not visible to the human eye may be classified in what way?',
    answer: 'Arthrokinematic',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Arthrokinematic|Osteokinematic|Anterior|Posterior',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question: 'How should an eccentric muscle action be described?',
    answer:
      'The development of muscle tension during lengthening of the contractile tissue',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The development of muscle tension during lengthening of the contractile tissue|The development of muscle tension during shortening of the contractile tissue|The development of muscle tension at a fixed speed during both shortening and lengthening of the contractile tissue|The development of muscle tension without shortening or lengthening of the contractile tissue',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question:
      'Stored energy from an efficiently functioning stretch-shortening cycle is released during which muscle action?',
    answer: 'Concentric',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Concentric|Eccentric|Isokinetic|Isometric',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question:
      'Which of the following examples describes a muscle that is functioning as an antagonist?',
    answer: 'The biceps brachii being active during elbow extension',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The biceps brachii being active during elbow extension|The serratus anterior being active during shoulder flexion|The infraspinatus being active during shoulder external rotation|The transversus abdominus being active during hip extension',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 7',
    topic: 'Chapter 7',
    question:
      'In what plane of movement do shoulder horizontal adduction and abduction occur?',
    answer: 'Transverse',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Transverse|Frontal|Sagittal|Dorsal',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question:
      'If someone were performing repeated sprints with each sprint lasting between 30 and 90 seconds, which energy system would be contributing the most to ATP production during this activity?',
    answer: 'Glycolysis',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Glycolysis|The ATP-PC system|Oxidative phosphorylation|The electron transport chain',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question:
      'When a person loses body weight, what is the only way that mass is lost?',
    answer: 'As exhaled carbon dioxide',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'As exhaled carbon dioxide|As water|As ATP|As exhaled oxygen',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'Why is nonexercise activity thermogenesis (NEAT) important?',
    answer: 'NEAT can be protective against obesity.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'NEAT can be protective against obesity.|NEAT can increase cardiorespiratory fitness.|NEAT can increase muscle mass.|NEAT can decrease the resting metabolic rate.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'What two factors define any form or type of exercise?',
    answer: 'Intensity and duration',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Intensity and duration|Duration and time|Intensity and speed|Speed and complexity',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'What are triglycerides?',
    answer: 'The stored form of fat',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The stored form of fat\n' +
      '|A substrate for high-intensity exercise\n' +
      '|The stored form of carbohydrate\n' +
      '|A substrate for anaerobic exercise\n' +
      '',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question:
      'If someone went out for a 5-mile jog with their friend, which energy system would provide most of the ATP for this activity?',
    answer: 'Oxidative phosphorylation',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Oxidative phosphorylation|Glycolysis|The ATP-PC system|Beta-oxidation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'Which of the following is a ketone body?',
    answer: 'Acetoacetic acid',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Acetoacetic acid|Glycogen|Pyruvate|Lactic acid',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'Food is composed of which three compounds?',
    answer: 'Carbohydrates, fats, and proteins',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Carbohydrates, fats, and proteins|ATP, glucose, and pyruvate|Ketones, insulin, and ADP|Amino acids, ATP, and glycogen',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'Which nutrient has the highest thermic effect?',
    answer: 'Protein',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Protein|Fat|Carbohydrate|Glycogen',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'What is defined as steady-state exercise?',
    answer: 'Aerobic exercise performed at a constant intensity',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Aerobic exercise performed at a constant intensity|Exercise that goes on for a long time|Exercise performed for a short duration of time|Exercise that burns a lot of calories',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question:
      'Before carbohydrates, fat, or protein can enter the citric acid cycle (CAC), they need to be converted to what common molecule?',
    answer: 'Acetyl CoA',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Acetyl CoA|ATP|Pyruvate|Amino acids',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'What does the electron transport chain (ETC) do?',
    answer: 'The ETC uses a hydrogen gradient to create ATP.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The ETC uses a hydrogen gradient to create ATP.|The ETC uses an oxygen gradient to create ATP.|The ETC uses proteins to create ADP.|The ETC uses proteins to create hydrogen ions.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'What is the ventilatory threshold 1 (VT1)?',
    answer:
      'The point at which the body switches to using carbohydrates to provide at least half the fuel for exercise',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The point at which the body switches to using carbohydrates to provide at least half the fuel for exercise|The point at which the body switches to using mostly fat as fuel for exercise|The point at which the body uses mostly protein as fuel for exercise|The point at which a person can no longer talk during exercise',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'What is a kilocalorie (kcal)?',
    answer:
      'The amount of energy needed to raise 1 kilogram of water by 1 degree Celsius. It is also the same thing as 1 food calorie.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The amount of energy needed to raise 1 kilogram of water by 1 degree Celsius. It is also the same thing as 1 food calorie.\n' +
      '|Unlike 1 food calorie, this is the amount of energy needed to raise 1 kilogram of water by 1 degree Celsius.\n' +
      '|The amount of energy needed to raise 1 pound of water by 1 degree Celsius. It is also the same thing as 1 food calorie.\n' +
      '|The amount of energy needed to raise 1 kilogram of water by 1 degree Celsius. It is equal to 1,000 food calories.\n' +
      '',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question:
      'Which of the following is a limiting factor for how long anaerobic glycolysis can proceed?',
    answer: 'Free hydrogen ions',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Free hydrogen ions|Lack of fatty acids|Depletion of phosphocreatine|Lack of pyruvate',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'What is excess postexercise oxygen consumption (EPOC)?',
    answer:
      'EPOC is the increase in aerobic metabolism above baseline that occurs for a period after exercise.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'EPOC is the increase in aerobic metabolism above baseline that occurs for a period after exercise.|EPOC is the faster rate of glycolysis that occurs after exercise.|EPOC is the increase in breathing rate that occurs during rest periods between exercise intervals.|EPOC is the increase in protein breakdown that occurs after exercise.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question:
      'Which of the following would make a person better at oxidizing fat?',
    answer: 'Having more mitochondria in their muscle',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Having more mitochondria in their muscle|Having more fat stored on their body|Having less oxygen delivery to the muscle|Having more glycogen stored in their muscle',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'What are the building blocks of body proteins?',
    answer: 'Amino acids',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Amino acids|Triglycerides|Glucose|Ketone bodies',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'What are essential amino acids?',
    answer:
      'Amino acids that must be consumed because they cannot be created by the body',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Amino acids that must be consumed because they cannot be created by the body|Amino acids that can be synthesized by the body|Amino acids responsible for protein synthesis|The only type of amino acid found in protein sources',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question:
      'Before amino acids can be used to make ATP, what process do they have to go through?',
    answer: 'Gluconeogenesis',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Gluconeogenesis|Glycolysis|Oxidative phosphorylation|Oxidation',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question:
      'If pyruvate is being created via glycolysis faster than oxygen can be delivered to the muscle, what will happen to the pyruvate?',
    answer: 'The pyruvate will be converted to lactate.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The pyruvate will be converted to lactate.|The pyruvate will be oxidized via oxidative phosphorylation.|The pyruvate will be stored in the muscle.|The pyruvate will be converted to acetyl CoA.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'What is the resting metabolic rate (RMR)?',
    answer:
      'RMR is the number of calories that the body uses at rest to function.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'RMR is the number of calories that the body uses at rest to function.|RMR is the number of calories burned after exercise.|RMR is the number of calories burned through digestion.|RMR is the number of calories burned through fidgeting.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'What is the name of the stored form of glucose?',
    answer: 'Glycogen',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Glycogen|Pyruvate|Glycolysis|Triglycerides',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'What is the definition of energy balance?',
    answer: 'When daily food intake is matched to energy needs',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'When daily food intake is matched to energy needs|When protein intake is higher than protein breakdown|When carbohydrates are consumed before a workout|When daily food intake is consistent',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question:
      'A client plans to go for a 10-mile run, but they become fatigued after 7 miles, so they stop. What is the most likely cause of this fatigue?',
    answer: 'Glycogen stores were exhausted.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Glycogen stores were exhausted.|Fatty acid stores were exhausted.|Phosphocreatine was depleted.|ADP was depleted.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question:
      'Which of the following components of total daily energy expenditure (TDEE) is responsible for the most energy expenditure throughout the day?',
    answer: 'Resting metabolic rate (RMR)',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Resting metabolic rate (RMR)\n' +
      '|Thermic effect of food (TEF)\n' +
      '|Exercise activity thermogenesis (EAT)\n' +
      '|Nonexercise activity thermogenesis (NEAT)\n' +
      '',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 8',
    topic: 'Chapter 8',
    question: 'What is bioenergetics?',
    answer: 'The study of the ways in which food is turned into energy',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The study of the ways in which food is turned into energy|The study of metabolism during exercise|The study of weight loss|The study of aerobic metabolism',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'During the course of a training session, a client remarks that he is "cutting out all carbs" from his diet and just eating protein and vegetables to lose weight. How might you best respond to this, while staying within your scope of practice as a fitness professional?',
    answer:
      'Carbohydrates are an important source of fuel for our body, and it is unnecessary to avoid them for weight loss. Cutting carbs may lead to inadequate fuel for optimal training, which can compromise weight-loss efforts.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Carbohydrates are an important source of fuel for our body, and it is unnecessary to avoid them for weight loss. Cutting carbs may lead to inadequate fuel for optimal training, which can compromise weight-loss efforts.|Carbohydrates contribute excess calories in our diet, and avoiding them is an effective weight-loss strategy during training.|Carbohydrates are not required unless training for long periods of time; so, as long as sessions are kept short, this strategy should be fine.|Carbohydrates provide more calories per gram than protein and fat, so they should be limited for effective weight loss.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'A client looking to add muscle and bulk over the next few months asks for advice on how to consume extra calories. Which of the following would be the most appropriate advice, while remaining within scope of practice?',
    answer: 'Suggest she increase meal frequency and portion sizes at meals.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Suggest she increase meal frequency and portion sizes at meals.|Recommend she eat high-calorie "cheat meals" more often.|Suggest she increase consumption of high-calorie foods such as ice cream, pizza, and cake.|Recommend she increase only her protein intake at every meal.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'You read an article in a popular magazine explaining the weight-loss benefits of including a certain nutrient in your diet. What should you consider in deciding if this is credible nutrition information?',
    answer:
      'Is the information supported by research, and has it been reviewed by other qualified individuals?',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Is the information supported by research, and has it been reviewed by other qualified individuals?|Has the information been reported on the news and in other media?|Is the nutrient available as a supplement, given the purported weight-loss benefits?|Is the magazine article in a recent publication or is it outdated?',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'A client asks you to provide her with a meal plan specifying how many calories and grams of protein, carbohydrates, and fat she should eat for weight loss. What is the best way to respond to her request to stay within scope of practice?',
    answer:
      'Explain that providing specific nutrient recommendations is outside your scope of practice, and then refer the client to a registered dietitian or licensed nutritionist for nutrition counseling.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Explain that providing specific nutrient recommendations is outside your scope of practice, and then refer the client to a registered dietitian or licensed nutritionist for nutrition counseling.|Agree to review her diet and provide her with a meal plan with specific recommendations for calories and macronutrients.|Provide her with an online 1,200-calorie meal plan for weight loss.|Explain that providing specific nutrient recommendations is outside your scope of practice, then suggest that she look up weight-loss meal plans on the internet.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'What is the optimal amount of protein per meal for muscle protein synthesis?',
    answer: '20 to 40 g',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: '20 to 40 g|15 to 20 g|30 to 50 g|60 to 70 g',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'Which part of a food label would help a client review the ingredients in a food product?',
    answer: 'The ingredients list',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The ingredients list|The nutrition facts panel|The nutrition label|The percent daily values',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'According to current research, what is the optimal range of daily protein intake to maximize muscle protein synthesis?',
    answer: '1.6 to 2.2 g/kg of body weight',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      '1.6 to 2.2 g/kg of body weight|3.5 to 5.0 g/kg of body weight|0.8 to 1.0 g/kg of body weight|2.4 to 3.5 g/kg of body weight',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'During short, high-intensity exercise, what is the primary fuel source for the body?',
    answer: 'Carbohydrates',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Carbohydrates|Lipids|Proteins|Amino acids',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question: 'What is glycogen?',
    answer: 'The storage form of carbohydrate in animals and humans',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The storage form of carbohydrate in animals and humans|The storage form of carbohydrate in plants|The enzyme that promotes carbohydrate breakdown in humans|The enzyme that promotes carbohydrate storage in humans and animals',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'Which of the following hydration options would be most appropriate for exercise lasting over 90 minutes, or shorter-duration exercise in warm temperatures with heavy perspiration?',
    answer: 'Sports drink or electrolyte tablets mixed with water',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Sports drink or electrolyte tablets mixed with water|Water mixed with fruit juice|Plain water|Fruit juice',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'Which of the following foods is the most likely to be a good source of omega-3 fatty acids?',
    answer: 'Salmon',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Salmon|Grilled chicken|Beef|Milk',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question: 'What are the three categories within the lipid family?',
    answer: 'Triglycerides, phospholipids, and sterols',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Triglycerides, phospholipids, and sterols|Cholesterol, omega-3s, and omega-6s|Saturated, unsaturated, and hydrogenated fats|Saturated fat, unsaturated fat, and cholesterol',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'Apart from energy intake and physical activity, which of the following factors also influence weight management?',
    answer: 'Hormones and medications',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Hormones and medications|Body temperature|Blood flow|Vitamin and mineral supplements',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'Which of the macronutrients has the highest thermic effect of food (TEF)?',
    answer: 'Protein',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Protein|Carbohydrates|Lipids|Glucose',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'Which of the following vitamins or groups of vitamins plays a key role in energy metabolism?',
    answer: 'B vitamins',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'B vitamins|Vitamin C|Fat-soluble vitamins|Water-soluble vitamins',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'Carbohydrate intake prior to intense or long-duration exercise serves which of the following functions?',
    answer:
      'It replenishes glycogen stores and provides adequate fuel for performance.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'It replenishes glycogen stores and provides adequate fuel for performance.|It is the primary energy source for low-intensity and long-duration exercise.|It provides adequate energy for muscle protein synthesis during training.|It replenishes depleted amino acid stores prior to high-intensity training.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question: 'What statement best describes the category of simple sugars?',
    answer:
      'Single- or double-molecule sugars that are easily absorbed by the body',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Single- or double-molecule sugars that are easily absorbed by the body|Sugar syrups that are easily absorbed by the body|Sugars that are dissolved into liquid for consumption|Sugars that have been added to packaged foods',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'You hear a client remark that she does not want to include any fat in her diet because she wants to avoid gaining weight. How might you respond, while staying within your scope of practice?',
    answer:
      'Some fats are essential and required in the diet for important physiological processes. Avoiding all fats might lead to deficiencies.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Some fats are essential and required in the diet for important physiological processes. Avoiding all fats might lead to deficiencies.|Fats provide more calories per gram than protein and carbohydrate, so avoiding them is a good strategy for weight management.|Fats are not an essential part of our diet and can be limited to avoid unnecessary calories.|Fats can be a source of extra calories in the diet, but they should be eaten to supply adequate energy for our brain.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question: 'What are the three macronutrients?',
    answer: 'Protein, carbohydrates, and lipids',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Protein, carbohydrates, and lipids|Vitamins, minerals, and phytonutrients|Protein, carbohydrates, and fluids|Carbohydrates, protein, and vitamins',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'A client who is training with you to improve his body composition states that he only sleeps 4 or 5 hours a night because he thinks that any more is a waste of time. How might you respond to him in view of his body composition goals?',
    answer:
      'Explain that adequate sleep is important in regulating hunger and satiety hormones, and that chronic sleep deprivation is detrimental for weight management.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Explain that adequate sleep is important in regulating hunger and satiety hormones, and that chronic sleep deprivation is detrimental for weight management.|Explain that 4 or 5 hours may not be enough for his requirements and that he should aim for 6 to 7 hours per day.|Explain that as long as he spends the extra hours engaged in physical activity, he should be able to meet his body composition goals.|Express understanding that he has a busy schedule and that sleep may not be a priority, and explain that this should not affect his body composition goals, as sleep and weight are unrelated.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'A client asks you how she could lose fat as quickly as possible for a beach vacation next weekend. Which of the following is the best way to respond to her question?',
    answer:
      'Explain that fat loss takes time and is best achieved with a moderate calorie deficit sustained over a period of time. Rapid weight loss usually results in loss of water weight and lean muscle mass, and it is not advisable.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Explain that fat loss takes time and is best achieved with a moderate calorie deficit sustained over a period of time. Rapid weight loss usually results in loss of water weight and lean muscle mass, and it is not advisable.|Explain that fat loss occurs in a caloric deficit and she should cut her caloric intake drastically over the next week to drop fat fast.|Suggest that she avoid eating carbohydrates during the week to promote fat loss.|Suggest that she avoid eating any fat during the week to promote fat loss.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question: 'What types of foods provide all the essential amino acids?',
    answer: 'Animal proteins',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Animal proteins|Plant proteins|Legumes|Fortified foods',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'How much fluid is recommended for rehydration after an intense training session or event?',
    answer: '1.25 times the amount of body weight lost during the activity',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      '1.25 times the amount of body weight lost during the activity|Twice the amount of body weight lost during the activity|2 to 3 liters of fluid|12 to 15 ounces of fluid',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question: 'How many calories are in 1 gram of protein?',
    answer: '4',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: '4|6|9|2',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 9',
    topic: 'Chapter 9',
    question:
      'Which of the following would be a helpful and sustainable strategy for achieving a moderate calorie deficit for fat loss?',
    answer: 'Replacing high-calorie foods with leaner substitutes',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Replacing high-calorie foods with leaner substitutes|Avoiding a food group (e.g., fats or carbohydrates)|Limiting meals to once a day|Replacing high-fiber foods with low-fiber options',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 1',
    topic: 'Chapter 1',
    question: 'Which condition is an example of a chronic disease?',
    answer: 'Type 2 diabetes',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Type 2 diabetes|Flu|Strep throat|Appendicitis',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 1',
    topic: 'Chapter 1',
    question: 'Which statement best describes the term deconditioned?',
    answer:
      'A state in which a person may have a combination of muscle imbalances, poor flexibility, insufficient endurance, or limited joint stability',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A state in which a person may have a combination of muscle imbalances, poor flexibility, insufficient endurance, or limited joint stability|A state in which the individual is out of breath when climbing a flight of stairs|A state in which a person is dealing with a chronic health condition|A state in which a person is overweight or obese and at risk for diabetes',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 3',
    topic: 'Chapter 3',
    question:
      'When family members are not supportive of exercise-related behaviors, it can be viewed as which of the following?',
    answer: 'A barrier to exercise',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A barrier to exercise|An influence on exercise|Amotivation to exercise|Ambivalence toward exercise',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 3',
    topic: 'Chapter 3',
    question: 'Empathy is best described as?',
    answer: 'The ability to identify with how another person feels',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The ability to identify with how another person feels|Providing instrumental support to an individual|Listening to a client but not providing any support|Being positive and outgoing during training sessions',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 3',
    topic: 'Chapter 3',
    question:
      'The role of psychology in fitness and wellness is strongly rooted in which area?',
    answer: 'Behavioral change',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Behavioral change|Eating disorders|Social physique anxiety|Depression',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 3',
    topic: 'Chapter 3',
    question:
      'Unrealistic goals can become a barrier when which of the following happens?',
    answer: 'When goals are not adjusted',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'When goals are not adjusted|When process goals are too specific|When outcome goals are objective|When only one goal is set',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 3',
    topic: 'Chapter 3',
    question:
      'A known relationship between sleep and exercise is demonstrated by which statement?',
    answer:
      'Increasing physical activity to at least 150 minutes per week at a moderate intensity can decrease symptoms of insomnia.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Increasing physical activity to at least 150 minutes per week at a moderate intensity can decrease symptoms of insomnia.|Resistance training has not been shown to have any positive effect on sleep disturbances.|In order for exercise to improve sleep, it must be coupled with medication.|Getting 10 minutes a day of physical activity is all that is needed to improve insomnia.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 4',
    topic: 'Chapter 4',
    question:
      'What part of a SMART goal involves being able to track progress?',
    answer: 'Measurable',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Measurable|Specific|Attainable|Timely',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'What is the function of the neuromuscular junction?',
    answer: 'The site where the nervous system and muscle fibers communicate',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The site where the nervous system and muscle fibers communicate|The site of muscular contractions|The sliding filament theory|Exposing actin-binding sites',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'A person walks differently when they move from a sidewalk onto the sand. This is regulated by what function?',
    answer: 'Motor function',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: "Motor function|Muscle function|Neuroplasticity|Wolff's law",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'Which part of a cell is responsible for using nutrients to create energy for the cell?',
    answer: 'Mitochondria',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Mitochondria|Organelles|Effector sites|Electrolytes',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'Which type of muscle fiber is predominantly used during movements that require high levels of force and power, such as a sprint?',
    answer: 'Type II',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Type II|Type I|Type III|Type Ia',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'What is the name of the specialized cell that is the functional unit of the nervous system?',
    answer: 'Neuron',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Neuron|Axon|Nucleus|Spindles',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'Which joint is the most mobile, able to move in all three directions?',
    answer: 'Ball-and-socket',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Ball-and-socket|Pivot|Saddle|Hinge',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'What are the two components of a sarcomere?',
    answer: 'Actin and myosin',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Actin and myosin|Epimysium and endomysium|Tropomyosin and troponin|Muscle fiber and muscle cell',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'Which type of joint includes the sutures of the skull?',
    answer: 'Nonsynovial',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Nonsynovial|Ball-and-socket|Pivot|Condyloid',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'What is the concept that describes the human body as a chain of interdependent links that work together to perform movement?',
    answer: 'Kinetic chain',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Kinetic chain|Golgi tendon organ|Nervous system|Proprioception',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      "When a client's heart rate is raised during cardio activities, this is being caused by which system?",
    answer: 'Sympathetic nervous system',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Sympathetic nervous system|Parasympathetic nervous system|Somatic nervous system|Central nervous system',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'What is the correct order of fascia, starting with the most superficial?',
    answer: 'Epimysium, perimysium, endomysium',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Epimysium, perimysium, endomysium|Endomysium, perimysium, epimysium|Perimysium, endomysium, epimysium|Epimysium, endomysium, perimysium',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'Humans can learn new things at any stage of life, due to which process that causes the brain to reform neural pathways?',
    answer: 'Neuroplasticity',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Neuroplasticity|Neurocircuitry|Neuromotor skills|Remodeling',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'What is the purpose of the intervertebral discs?',
    answer: 'They act as shock absorbers.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "They act as shock absorbers.|They minimize movement of the spine.|They support most of the body's weight and are attached to many back muscles.|They provide support for the head.",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'Weight-bearing exercise helps strengthen bones through what process?',
    answer: 'Remodeling',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Remodeling|Lengthening|Osteoporosis|Neuroplasticity',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'What is the fibrous tissue that connects bone to bone?',
    answer: 'Ligament',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Ligament|Collagen|Tendon|Elastin',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'What are the three types of muscles in the body?',
    answer: 'Skeletal, cardiac, and smooth',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Skeletal, cardiac, and smooth|Actin, myosin, and sarcomere|Somatic, autonomic, and peripheral|Cervical, thoracic, and lumbar',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'What is a characteristic of a type II muscle fiber?',
    answer: 'Short-term contractions',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Short-term contractions|Increased oxygen delivery|Slow to fatigue|Smaller in size',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'Which of these is one of the major curvatures of the spine from a posterior view?',
    answer: 'Concave lumbar curve',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Concave lumbar curve\n' +
      '|Convex lumbar curve\n' +
      '|Convex cervical curve\n' +
      '|Concave thoracic curve\n' +
      '',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question:
      'Which division of the skeleton is made up of the arms, legs, and pelvic girdle?',
    answer: 'Appendicular',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Appendicular|Axial|Lateral|Peripheral',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 5',
    topic: 'Chapter 5',
    question: 'What best describes the all-or-nothing principle?',
    answer: 'A motor unit will either contract maximally or not at all.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A motor unit will either contract maximally or not at all.|All muscle fibers contract, or none at all do.|The switch from type I to type II muscle fibers|The switch from type IIa to type IIx muscle fibers',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question:
      'Which of the following hormones, if increased at baseline, may be indicative of overtraining?',
    answer: 'Cortisol',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Cortisol|Testosterone|Growth hormone|Thyroxin',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question:
      'Which of the following effects may be experienced with overtraining?',
    answer: 'High levels of cortisol, which lead to a catabolic environment',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'High levels of cortisol, which lead to a catabolic environment|Elevated levels of cortisol, which lead to an anabolic environment|Lower levels of cortisol, which lead to an anabolic environment|Low levels of cortisol, which lead to an environment that is anabolic',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question:
      'Which heart chamber gathers oxygenated blood coming to the heart from the lungs?',
    answer: 'Left atrium',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Left atrium|Right atrium|Left ventricle|Pulmonary veins',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question:
      'Food in the stomach is processed and then passes into what anatomical structure?',
    answer: 'Duodenum of the small intestine',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Duodenum of the small intestine|Duodenum of the large intestine|The ileum of the small intestine|The ileum of the large intestine',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question:
      'Which of the following hormones have an anabolic function and have been shown to increase up to 48 hours following resistance training?',
    answer: 'Insulin-like growth factor (IGF)',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Insulin-like growth factor (IGF)|Glucagon|Cortisol|Calcitonin',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question:
      'What structure in the heart transfers the electrical signal from the sinoatrial (SA) node to the atrioventricular (AV) node?',
    answer: 'Internodal pathway',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Internodal pathway|Intercalated discs|Right bundle branch|Left bundle branch',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 6',
    topic: 'Chapter 6',
    question:
      'What mechanism is responsible for increasing the rate of heart conduction?',
    answer: 'Activation of the sympathetic nervous system',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Activation of the sympathetic nervous system|Activation of the parasympathetic nervous system|Activation of the intercalated discs|Activation of sarcomeres',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question:
      'Which two electrolytes are most commonly supplemented by athletes to replace those lost in sweat?',
    answer: 'Sodium and potassium',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Sodium and potassium|Sodium and calcium|Magnesium and sodium|Potassium and manganese',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question: 'Can supplements contain food allergens?',
    answer:
      'Yes, and if they do contain allergens, they should be listed on the label.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Yes, and if they do contain allergens, they should be listed on the label.|No, because supplements are not food.|No, because supplements are not real food.|Yes, but only if the supplement is sourced from whole foods.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question:
      'What percentage of alpha-linolenic acid (ALA) converts to a biologically available form called eicosapentaenoic acid (EPA)?',
    answer: 'About 5-15%',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'About 5-15%|About 30%|About 50%|About 90%',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question: 'Which vitamin is the most transient?',
    answer: 'Vitamin C',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Vitamin C|Vitamin D|Vitamin E|Vitamin A',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question: 'The B vitamins have a primary role in what?',
    answer: 'Macronutrient metabolism',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Macronutrient metabolism|Muscle contraction|Hydration|Cancer prevention',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question:
      'Which of the following is a banned substance in the United States?',
    answer: 'Dimethylamylamine (DMAA)',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Dimethylamylamine (DMAA)|Caffeine|Creatine|Hordenine',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question:
      'The most well-known and well-researched effect of omega-3 fats relates to which of the following?',
    answer: 'Heart health',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Heart health|Athletic performance|Endocrine health|Bone health',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question:
      'Accumulating too much of a vitamin or mineral in the body may lead to what?',
    answer: 'Toxicity',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Toxicity|Improved performance|Deficiency|Better outcomes',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question:
      'Which of the following is true about the biologically active forms of vitamins?',
    answer:
      'Biologically active forms are most effective for augmenting body levels.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Biologically active forms are most effective for augmenting body levels.|Biologically active forms lead to toxicity.|Biologically active forms lead to deficiency.|Biologically active forms are less efficient.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question: 'Which of the following is true of protein shakes?',
    answer: 'They are convenient options for increasing protein intake.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'They are convenient options for increasing protein intake.|They are required to build muscle.|They are dangerous and should be avoided.|They are a poor choice for recovery.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question:
      'Which organization must approve a supplement prior to it being sold?',
    answer: 'Supplements do not require approval prior to sale.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Supplements do not require approval prior to sale.|Food and Drug Administration (FDA)|World Anti-Doping Agency (WADA)|European Food Safety Authority (EFSA)',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question: 'Which vitamin has an increased risk of causing toxicity?',
    answer: 'Vitamin A',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Vitamin A|Vitamin C|Vitamin B12|Vitamin B6',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question:
      'What is the best definition of essential when discussing human nutrition?',
    answer:
      'Must be obtained in the diet, as the body is incapable of producing the nutrient on its own',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Must be obtained in the diet, as the body is incapable of producing the nutrient on its own|Contained within healthy food items|Needed to build muscle|Another word for macronutrients',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question:
      'Compared to water-soluble vitamins, which of the following is true about fat-soluble vitamins?',
    answer:
      'Fat-soluble vitamins take longer to accumulate in and deplete from the body.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Fat-soluble vitamins take longer to accumulate in and deplete from the body.|Fat-soluble vitamins are better for improving overall health.|Fat-soluble vitamins accumulate in and deplete quickly from the body.|Fat-soluble vitamins are not as healthy because fat is unhealthy.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 10',
    topic: 'Chapter 10',
    question:
      'Which of the following is a major nutritional contributor to muscle protein synthesis?',
    answer: 'The essential amino acids',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'The essential amino acids|Vitamins|Minerals|Caffeine',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 11',
    topic: 'Chapter 11',
    question:
      'For which population is the 1.5-mile (2.4-km) run test considered most valid?',
    answer: 'College-aged athletes',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'College-aged athletes|Older adults|Individuals recovering from an injury|Deconditioned individuals',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 11',
    topic: 'Chapter 11',
    question:
      'The PAR-Q+ and preparticipation process reflects what three health indicators?',
    answer:
      "An individual's current level of physical activity, the presence of signs and symptoms of disease, and the individual's desired exercise intensity",
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "An individual's current level of physical activity, the presence of signs and symptoms of disease, and the individual's desired exercise intensity|An individual's current level of physical activity, age, and weight|An individual's desired exercise intensity, body composition, and gender|An individual's habits related to exercise, diet, and sleep",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 11',
    topic: 'Chapter 11',
    question:
      'Which of the following represents a criterion for terminating an exercise test or exercise bout that involves exertion?',
    answer: 'Any indication of chest pain or angina-like symptoms',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Any indication of chest pain or angina-like symptoms|An elevation of systolic blood pressure to 220 mm Hg|Labored or heavy breathing associated with exertion|Failure of diastolic blood pressure to rise by more than 15 mm Hg',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 11',
    topic: 'Chapter 11',
    question:
      'Where is the appropriate location to take a waist circumference measurement?',
    answer:
      'At the narrowest point of the waist, below the rib cage and just above the top of the hip bones (while standing)',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'At the narrowest point of the waist, below the rib cage and just above the top of the hip bones (while standing)|At the widest portion of the buttocks (while standing with feet together)|At the largest circumference immediately below the gluteal fold (while standing)|At the widest point of the waist (while seated)',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 11',
    topic: 'Chapter 11',
    question:
      'Which of the following intensities best represents VT2 during the incremental test protocol?',
    answer:
      'When the individual responds with "no" when asked, “Can you speak competently?”',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'When the individual responds with "no" when asked, “Can you speak competently?”|When the individual responds with "yes" when asked, “Can you speak competently?”|When the individual says it is "somewhat easy" to talk during the activity|When the individual says it is "challenging" to speak during the activity',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 11',
    topic: 'Chapter 11',
    question: 'What does BMI (body mass index) assess for?',
    answer: "Whether a person's weight is appropriate for their height",
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "Whether a person's weight is appropriate for their height|Body fat and lean mass composition|Overall level of physical fitness|An accurate measure of obesity status for all individuals",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 11',
    topic: 'Chapter 11',
    question: 'What step height is used for the YMCA 3-minute step test?',
    answer: '12 inches',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: '12 inches|16 inches|14 inches|10 inches',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 11',
    topic: 'Chapter 11',
    question:
      'Which of the following blood pressure readings would classify an individual as having stage 1 hypertension?',
    answer: '135/80 mm Hg',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: '135/80 mm Hg|118/78 mm Hg|124/80 mm Hg|143/92 mm Hg',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 11',
    topic: 'Chapter 11',
    question: 'What is the most valid measurement of aerobic fitness?',
    answer: 'VO2max',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'VO2max\n' +
      '|YMCA 3-minute step test\n' +
      '|Rockport walk test\n' +
      '|1.5-mile (2.4-km) run test\n' +
      '',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 11',
    topic: 'Chapter 11',
    question:
      'What location on the body does NASM recommend for measuring the resting heart rate?',
    answer: 'Radial pulse',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Radial pulse|Carotid pulse|Pedal pulse|Femoral pulse',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which muscle would be considered underactive, leading to the excessive forward trunk lean during the overhead squat assessment?',
    answer: 'Gluteus maximus',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Hip flexor complex|Gastrocnemius and soleus|Gluteus maximus|Rectus abdominis',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which muscle would be considered underactive, leading to shoulder elevation during the pushing assessment?',
    answer: 'Lower trapezius',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Lower trapezius|Cervical extensors|Serratus anterior|Upper trapezius',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'For which movement impairment would you see the knees bow outward?',
    answer: 'Knee varus',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Knee dominance|Knee varus|Knee valgus|Excessive anterior pelvic tilt',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which of the following exercises is typically used to measure maximum strength of the lower extremities?',
    answer: 'Squat',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Overhead squat|Squat|Single-leg squat|Lunge',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which of the following tests is designed to test reaction capabilities, acceleration, and maximal sprinting speed?',
    answer: '40-yard dash',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Overhead squat|Lower extremity functional test (LEFT)|40-yard dash|Pro shuttle',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which muscle would be considered overactive, leading to the low back arching during the overhead squat assessment?',
    answer: 'Hip flexor complex',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Gluteus maximus|Hamstrings complex|Gluteus medius|Hip flexor complex',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question: 'Which muscles are typically overactive when the feet turn out?',
    answer: 'Gastrocnemius and soleus',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Upper trapezius|Gastrocnemius and soleus|Hip flexors|Adductor complex',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      "Which movement assessment is a good assessment of a client's balance during movement?",
    answer: 'Single-leg squat',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Overhead squat|Push-up test|40-yard dash|Single-leg squat',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which type of assessment assesses the alignment of the body while in motion?',
    answer: 'Dynamic posture assessment',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Dynamic posture assessment|Overhead squat assessment|Performance assessment|Static posture assessment',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which of the following tests is used to measure lower-extremity power?',
    answer: 'Vertical jump',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Lower extremity functional test (LEFT)|40-yard dash|Pro shuttle|Vertical jump',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which muscle would be considered underactive, leading to the low back arching during the overhead squat assessment?',
    answer: 'Gluteus maximus',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Latissimus dorsi|Gluteus maximus|Hip flexor complex|Lumbar extensors',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which muscle would be considered underactive, leading to shoulder elevation during the pulling assessment?',
    answer: 'Lower trapezius',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Cervical extensors|Serratus anterior|Upper trapezius|Lower trapezius',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'What do you visualize to detect the movement impairment of knee valgus?',
    answer: 'The knees collapsing inward',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The knees bowing outward|An upright trunk and knees in front of toes|The knees collapsing inward|The hip shifting toward one side or the other',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question: 'How often is it recommended to reassess clientele?',
    answer: 'Every month',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Every year|Every 6 months|Every week|Every month',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'What do you visualize to detect the movement impairment shoulder elevation?',
    answer: 'The shoulders moving upward toward the ears',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The trunk leaning forward|The arms falling forward|The shoulders moving upward toward the ears|The scapula protruding excessively from the back',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question: 'When is a muscle considered overactive?',
    answer:
      'When it is in a state of elevated neural activity (compared to its antagonist muscle), which causes the muscle to be held in a chronic state of contraction',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'When it is in a state of elevated neural activity (compared to its antagonist muscle), which causes the muscle to be held in a chronic state of relaxation|When a muscle is elongated and in a state of reduced neural activity|When it is in a state of elevated neural activity (compared to its antagonist muscle), which causes the muscle to be held in a chronic state of contraction|When a muscle is experiencing neural inhibition and limited neuromuscular recruitment',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question: 'How is lower crossed syndrome characterized?',
    answer: 'Anterior pelvic tilt and excessive lordosis of the lumbar spine',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Anterior pelvic tilt and excessive kyphosis of the lumbar spine|Flat feet, knee valgus, and internally rotated and adducted hips|Posterior pelvic tilt and excessive lordosis of the lumbar spine|Anterior pelvic tilt and excessive lordosis of the lumbar spine',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which muscle(s) may be overactive with knee valgus during the overhead squat?',
    answer: 'Tensor fascia latae and adductor complex',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Tensor fascia latae and adductor complex\n' +
      '|Gluteus maximus and medius\n' +
      '|Hip flexors\n' +
      '|Upper trapezius\n' +
      '',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question: 'What depth is suggested for the overhead squat assessment?',
    answer: 'Femur parallel to ground',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Femur parallel to ground|Knees to 45 degrees|Butt to heels|Full-depth squat',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which movement assessment is a global observation of the entire kinetic chain and recommended as the first movement assessment to use with all clients?',
    answer: 'Overhead squat',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Pulling assessment|Single-leg squat|Pushing assessment|Overhead squat',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question: 'Which muscles are typically underactive when the feet turn out?',
    answer: 'Anterior and posterior tibialis',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Anterior and posterior tibialis|Adductor complex|Abdominals|Upper trapezius',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which of the following tests is used to measure lateral speed and agility?',
    answer: 'Lower extremity functional test (LEFT)',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Vertical jump|Lower extremity functional test (LEFT)|40-yard dash|Pro shuttle',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which postural distortion is characterized by anterior pelvic tilt and excessive lordosis (extension) of the lumbar spine?',
    answer: 'Lower crossed syndrome',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Pes planus distortion syndrome|Excessive pronation|Upper crossed syndrome|Lower crossed syndrome',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which muscles are typically overactive in association with upper crossed syndrome?',
    answer: 'Upper trapezius',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Hip flexors|Lower trapezius|Adductor complex|Upper trapezius',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which muscle would be considered overactive, leading to shoulder elevation during the pushing assessment?',
    answer: 'Upper trapezius',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Latissimus dorsi|Upper trapezius|Infraspinatus|Lower trapezius',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which muscle would be considered underactive, leading to arms falling forward in the overhead squat assessment?',
    answer: 'Middle and lower trapezius',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Middle and lower trapezius|Pectoralis major|Latissimus dorsi|Teres major',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which muscles are typically overactive in association with lower crossed syndrome?',
    answer: 'Hip flexors and lumbar extensors',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Adductor complex|Hip flexors and lumbar extensors|Abdominals|Upper trapezius',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Chapter 12',
    topic: 'Chapter 12',
    question:
      'Which of the following exercises is typically used to measure maximum strength of the upper extremities during a pushing movement?',
    answer: 'Bench press strength assessment',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Bench press strength assessment|Overhead press assessment|Pulling assessment|Pushing assessment',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'When sequencing physiological assessments, which of the following would produce a better result if measured immediately after exercise rather than before exercise?',
    answer: 'Flexibility',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Flexibility|Body composition|Blood pressure|Resting heart rate',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question: 'How can diastolic blood pressure be defined?',
    answer:
      'The pressure in arteries and other blood vessels when the heart is at rest or between beats; the second (bottom) number recorded',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The pressure in arteries and other blood vessels when the heart is at rest or between beats; the second (bottom) number recorded\n' +
      '|The pressure in arteries and other blood vessels when the heart is contracting; the first (top) number recorded\n' +
      '|The measurement of the number of times a heart beats within a specified time period (usually 1 minute)\n' +
      '|The action of expanding the diameter of a blood vessel near the surface of the skin, which helps remove heat from the body\n' +
      '',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question: 'What step cadence is used during the YMCA 3-minute step test?',
    answer: 'A cadence of 96 steps per minute',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A cadence of 96 steps per minute|A cadence of 36 steps per minute|A cadence of 60 steps per minute|A cadence of 112 steps per minute',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question: 'What principle is hydrostatic underwater weighing based upon?',
    answer: "Archimedes' principle",
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      "Archimedes' principle|All-or-nothing principle|Principle of specificity|Davis's principle",
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'How many skinfold sites are measured when determining body composition using the Durnin-Womersley protocol?',
    answer: 'Four',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Four|Six|Seven|Three',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which muscles are typically underactive in association with pes planus distortion syndrome?',
    answer: 'Anterior and posterior tibialis, and gluteus maximus and medius',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Anterior and posterior tibialis, and gluteus maximus and medius|Adductor complex (inner thighs)|Hip flexors|Upper trapezius',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question: 'What are the five kinetic chain checkpoints?',
    answer: 'Feet and ankles, knees, LPHC, shoulders, and head and neck',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Feet and ankles, knees, LPHC, shoulders, and head and neck|Feet, ankles, knees, abdomen, and chest|Feet, ankles, knees, torso, and neck|Feet and ankles, LPHC, shoulders, head, and neck',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      "Where is it most common to take an individual's circumference measurement to assess health risk?",
    answer: 'Waist',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Waist|Hips|Thigh|Arm',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'What term refers to the ability of a test to produce consistent and repeatable results?',
    answer: 'Reliability',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Reliability|Relevance|Validity|Appropriateness',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which muscle would be considered overactive, leading to the excessive forward trunk lean during the overhead squat assessment?',
    answer: 'Hip flexors',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Hip flexors|Gluteus maximus|Hamstrings complex|Gluteus medius',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'If Joe takes a 6-second heart rate count on his client and notes 8 beats, what would his client’s heart rate be?',
    answer: '80 beats per minute',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      '80 beats per minute|72 beats per minute|66 beats per minute|64 beats per minute',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'The standard Jackson and Pollock 3-Site protocol for women requires skinfold measurements at which of the following sites?',
    answer: 'Suprailiac, thigh, and triceps',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Suprailiac, thigh, and triceps|Triceps, abdomen, and thigh|Chest, suprailiac, and abdomen|Abdomen, thigh, and suprailiac',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which skinfold sites are measured if determining body composition via the Durnin-Womersley protocol?',
    answer: 'Biceps, triceps, subscapular, and suprailiac',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Biceps, triceps, subscapular, and suprailiac|Triceps, abdomen, mid-axillary, and suprailiac|Triceps, subscapular, chest, and thigh|Biceps, mid-axillary, subscapular, and chest',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which muscles may be overactive with knee valgus during the overhead squat?',
    answer: 'Tensor fascia latae and adductor complex',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Tensor fascia latae and adductor complex|Gluteus maximus and medius|Hip flexors|Upper trapezius',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'What best defines a Physical Activity Readiness Questionnaire (PAR-Q+)?',
    answer:
      'A detailed questionnaire designed to assess an individual’s physical readiness to engage in structured exercise',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A detailed questionnaire designed to assess an individual’s physical readiness to engage in structured exercise|A screening tool used to evaluate the benefits and the risks associated with starting any type of exercise that is strenuous in nature|A questionnaire with lists of questions that pertain to health history and habits, such as exercise history, eating behaviors, and general lifestyle|A screening where the results indicate a need for medical clearance,\n' +
      'when one is not, in fact, needed',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which of the following waist-to-hip ratios (WHRs) places Amy (a female) in the high-risk category for cardiovascular disease?',
    answer: 'WHR of 0.88',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'WHR of 0.88|WHR of 0.72|WHR of 0.78|WHR of 0.83',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which muscles are typically underactive with knee valgus during the single-leg squat?',
    answer: 'Gluteus maximus and medius',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Gluteus maximus and medius|Adductor complex|Tensor fascia latae|Lower trapezius',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'In which BMI category would you classify Vincent if he has a BMI of 27?',
    answer: 'Overweight',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Overweight|Healthy weight|Obese|Class II obesity',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'What is a body composition assessment technique that estimates body fat percentage by measuring the resistance to the flow of electrical currents introduced into the body?',
    answer: 'Bioelectrical impedance analysis (BIA)',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Bioelectrical impedance analysis (BIA)|Skinfold measurements|Anthropometry|Body mass index\n' +
      '(BMI)',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which type of assessment evaluates the position of the musculoskeletal system while the body is standing still?',
    answer: 'Static posture assessment',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Static posture assessment|Overhead squat assessment|Dynamic posture assessment|Performance assessment',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which type of assessment measures overall strength, stability, muscular endurance, and agility?',
    answer: 'Performance assessment',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Performance assessment|Overhead squat assessment|Dynamic posture assessment|Static posture assessment',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which of the following exercises is typically used to measure muscular endurance of the upper extremities during a pushing movement?',
    answer: 'Push-up test',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Push-up test|Pushing assessment|Bench press strength assessment|Overhead press',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which of the following statements defines the chest skinfold location for men?',
    answer:
      'A diagonal fold taken half the distance between the anterior axillary line and the nipple',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'A diagonal fold taken half the distance between the anterior axillary line and the nipple\n' +
      '|A diagonal fold, 1 to 2 centimeters below the inferior angle of the scapula\n' +
      '|A diagonal fold taken immediately superior to and in line with the natural angle of the iliac crest (top portion of the hip bone), aligned with the anterior axillary line\n' +
      '|A vertical fold taken on the mid-axillary line at the level of the xiphoid process (which is typically just below the nipple line)\n' +
      '',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which postural distortion is characterized by a forward head and rounded shoulders?',
    answer: 'Upper crossed syndrome',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Upper crossed syndrome|Pes planus distortion syndrome|Lower crossed syndrome|Knee valgus',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which type of assessment is typically performed first in the assessment flow?',
    answer: 'Static posture',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Static posture|Single-leg squat|40-yard dash|Bench press strength',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'What are three postural distortion patterns to look for in static postural assessments?',
    answer:
      'Pes planus distortion syndrome, lower crossed syndrome, and upper crossed syndrome',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Pes planus distortion syndrome, lower crossed syndrome, and upper crossed syndrome|Pes planus distortion syndrome, knees cave inward, and arms fall forward|Knee dominance, upper crossed syndrome, and lower crossed syndrome|Low-back arches, shoulders elevate, and head juts forward',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question: 'How is upper crossed syndrome characterized?',
    answer: 'Forward head and protracted shoulders',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Forward head and protracted shoulders\n' +
      '|Anterior pelvic tilt and excessive lordosis of the lumbar spine\n' +
      '|Excessive forward lean and arms fall forward\n' +
      '|Flat feet, knee valgus, and internally rotated and adducted hips\n' +
      '',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'From the list of assessments provided, which should be conducted first to preserve its validity?',
    answer: 'Body composition',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'Body composition|Cardiorespiratory fitness|Muscular fitness|Flexibility',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'In most individuals, to what pressure is the blood pressure cuff inflated when measuring resting blood pressure?',
    answer:
      'The cuff is inflated to a value of 20 to 30 mm Hg above the point at which the pulse can no longer be felt at the wrist.',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The cuff is inflated to a value of 20 to 30 mm Hg above the point at which the pulse can no longer be felt at the wrist.|The cuff is inflated to a value 70 to 80 mm Hg above the point at which the pulse can no longer be felt at the wrist.|The cuff is inflated to a value 45 to 55 mm Hg above the point at which the pulse can no longer be felt at the wrist.|The cuff is inflated to a value 5 to 10 mm Hg above the point at which the pulse can no longer be felt at the wrist.',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which muscles are typically underactive in association with upper crossed syndrome?',
    answer: 'Lower trapezius',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Lower trapezius|Upper trapezius|Hip flexors|Abdominals',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which test would you select as the most appropriate when attempting to measure the overall fitness level of a fit college-aged athlete who competes on the school’s rugby team?',
    answer: 'The 1.5-mile (2.4-km) run test',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options:
      'The 1.5-mile (2.4-km) run test|YMCA 3-minute step test|Rockport 1-mile walk test|The talk test',
  },
  {
    source: 'NASM Personal Fitness Training: Section 4 Review',
    topic: 'Assessment',
    question:
      'Which term defines the degree to which a test specifically measures what it is intended to measure?',
    answer: 'Validity',
    type: 'Quiz',
    cert: 'NASM CPT',
    options: 'Validity|Appropriateness|Reliability|Relevance',
  },
]
